sub2smi by 블랙이글
알파 독
(Alpha Dog, 2006)
sub2smi by 열노(yeolno)
솔직하게 말해보라고요?
SONNY: You want to know
what this is all about?
You could say
it's about drugs or guns
마약, 살인, 뻔한 얘기로
몰아 붙이지 맙시다
or disaffected youth,
원하는 게 뭐든지 간에요
or whatever you like.
부모 맘을
얘기해 보자고요
But this whole thing
is about parenting.
당신도 부모라면
내 맘 알 거 아뇨
It's about taking care
of your children.
You take care of yours,
I take care of mine.
무슨 말씀이신지?
INTERVIEWER: I'm sorry,
I don't understand.
What does that mean?
That's all I have to say
about that subject.
Next question.
할 얘기 다 했소
다음 질문
Your son
was a drug dealer?
아드님이 마약 딜러죠?
A drug dealer? No.
Did he sell a little weed?
Yeah.
풀 쪼가리 좀 판 것 갖고!
A little weed?
He was a major supplier
to the San Gabriel Valley.
풀 쪼가리요?
LA지역은 싹쓸이 했다던데!
그건 아는 바 없소
I don't know
anything about that.
게다가 마약 대준 게
바로 아버지였고?
What about the D.A.'s
assertion that your son
got his marijuana from you?
And that you have ties
to organized crime?
경찰처럼 쪼잔하게
물고 늘어지시네!
What is this
amateur night bullshit?
꼬박꼬박 세금 내는
착한 시민한테 왜 이러나
This isn't an interrogation,
all right?
I'm a taxpayer
and I'm a citizen.
And you are a jerk-off.
진짜 속물은
바로 당신이야!
Did I tell you that?
클레어몬트, 캘리포니아
1999년 11월
조니, 12번 못 채우면
사내구실 못한다!
TIKO: Come on, Johnny, I don't
let fiend jump in the alley.
If you don't give me
fucking 12 reps,
I'm fucking your mom
and your girl.
뭐라고 내뱉었냐?
사내구실이 뭐 어째?
FRANKIE: Tell him, Tiko!
What'd you say?
I couldn't hear you.
You say you want
to suck my cock, right?
사이즈도 작은 놈이!
First you got to grow one.
내 거 팔뚝 만해!
JOHNNY: Shit, my dick's
so big it's got a knee.
(LAUGHING)
키 160에 커 봤자지!
TIKO: Five foot three,
hung like a flea.
젠장, 너무 더워
Fuck, it's hot
out there.
뭐야, 엘비스?
아직 대낮이거든!
What are you doing, Elvis?
Is it dark outside?
What?
I'm paying you
for a full day, right?
- 뭐?
- 해질 때까지 일해야지!
I've been here
since 10:00 this morning.
아침 10시부터
죽도록 해서 끝냈어
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
Fuck that shit.
I asked you a question.
지금이 밤이냐?
달 떴어?
Do you see
the fucking moon, Elvis?
- 밖이 훤한데!
- 내 엉덩이 보름달!
It's definitely daylight.
I'll show you my moon.
조니, 시킨 거 다했어
Johnny, I did everything
that you said.
청소에 음식과 음료도
냉장고에 정리 다 했고
The house is clean. I went
to the store. There's food
and beer in the fridge.
빨래하고, 개 밥 주고
잔디도 깎았다고!
The wash is done. Adolf's fed.
The grass is cut.
It's all done, man.
누가 빨리 하랬어?
Well, I guess
you shouldn't have
finished so fast, huh?
Shut the fuck up.
까불면 죽는다
Never mind that.
Shut the fuck up!
- 쟤들 말 무시해
- 죽는다고!
Get back to fucking work.
일하러 가
You want shit to do?
Go wash the floors.
Scrub out the toilets.
좋은 말 할 때 바닥이나 닦아
화장실 광도 내고
Or better yet,
pick up all the dog shit
in the backyard.
이미 다 했으면
정원에서 개똥 치우고
그래도 시간 남으면
그 똥 다시 뿌려
And if you finish too fast,
dump it out...
그 똥 또 치우면 되겠네!
ALL: And pick it
back up again.
닥치랬지!
Party's over, man.
Shut the fuck up, Pick.
- 똥 치울 집게 줄까?
- 예민하시긴!
FRANKIE: I can get you
a pooper scooper.
PICK: Why are you so touchy?
- 너희 죽는다
- 뭐?
That's messed up, man.
JOHNNY: What?
돈 언제 갚을 거야?
When am I going
to get my money, Elvis? When?
I told you.
I get my check on Thursday.
목요일에 월급 받으면
All right. Well,
how much is the check?
얼마 받는데?
I don't know.
It depends on the hours.
몰라, 시간 따라 달라
Well, how many hours
did you work, bitch?
몇 시간 일했는데?
I can't remember.
기억 안 나
Fucking deadbeat, man.
게으른 놈, 꺼져
Go on,
get the fuck out of here.
열 받은 또라이 퇴장이요
The walk of shame.
The walk of shame, man.
어이, 바비!
Yo! What up, little B?
- 바비 오냐?
- 911이야
What up, B?
It's 911.
8,500 달러
$8,500.
그렇게 많이?
All of it, huh?
- 꽤 되네!
- 그래
Surprise, surprise.
Yeah.
Okay.
좋아...
So?
몇 개나?
So I got this guy.
손님이 5개 사달래
내 건 2개
He wants five.
Plus my regular two.
총 7개 구해줘
So I figure
I'm going to need seven.
어떨지 모르겠어
I don't know, B. I don't...
물건이 많이 없는데
I don't like having
that much shit out.
잔금은 월요일에...
돈 걱정은 말고
I'm going to see my guy
on Monday and I'll clear you
right out, man.
봐줘라, 조니
He's good for it, Johnny.
You don't need to tell him
I'm good for it, man.
거지 적선하듯
할 거 없어
I'm not looking
for any fucking favors, J.T.
낼 거 내고
받을 건 받고!
If it makes sense, do it.
땡기면 하고...
꼴리면 엎어
If not, fuck it.
좋아
All right.
해보자
We'll try it.
넌 어디로 뜰 건데?
Where are you going, right?
잠수타면 안 되지!
TIKO: That's what
I'm talking about.
어디 엎어져 있든
돈 낼 땐 나타나라
But come Friday,
I don't want to hear
any fucking stories.
You won't.
걱정 마
SONNY: Be ready, be ready.
Soft hands, right?
Soft hands.
프로선수처럼 멋지게!
Nice. Nice.
That's major league stuff
right there, baby.
근사하게 빵 날려 봐
Grab a bat,
and I'll throw you a couple.
- 할아버지
- 어서 와라
Hey.
웬일이냐?
What do you say, Tarzan?
I need seven.
7개 주문이요
Seven?
- 7개나? 누군데?
- 바비
Seven? Who?
Bobby "911".
Yeah? Well,
we could put together.
설마 짭새랑 선 닿은
놈은 아니지?
I don't want
to get picked off.
All right.
아니에요
- 뭐 하던 놈인지 아냐?
- 그게...
You know where he's been?
Yeah.
그건 모르는데
느낌이 괜찮아요
I mean, I don't know,
but it feels good.
- 일 꼬이면 네 책임이다
- 당연하죠, 아빠
All right.
It's on you anyway, right?
It always is, Pop.
이 녀석 인물
훤한 것 좀 보게나
Hey, look at this kid.
How handsome he is.
Look at this!
- 여자들이 미치지?
- 아뇨, 이러지 마세요
You must be
knocking them dead.
You knocking them dead?
No. Let go of me.
So, what are you
doing tonight?
You chasing tail?
오늘 밤도 여자랑?
No, I'm just chilling.
아니, 쉴 거예요
On a Friday night?
여자 없이 금요일 밤을?
Sonny?
I know. I know.
- 그걸 믿으라고?
- 그러게요
멀쩡한 놈
호모인 줄 알았네
Don't make me wonder
about you, kid. You sound
like half a fucking fag.
- 하긴 좀 이상하더라니
- 물건이나 해 줘요
Always had my suspicions.
Just make the fucking call.
할애비 말 명심해
Wait a minute.
Remember what I told you.
여자는 한 명으로 안 돼
씨를 쫙쫙 뿌려야지!
Men are not supposed to be
monopolous. It's in our nature
to spread the seed.
자상도 하셔라
가자
Yeah, very poetic.
Come on. Come on.
안젤라도 괜찮지만
딴 여자랑도 해 봐야지
Angela's a nice girl and all,
but you got to plow
some fucking fields!
Did you hear me,
you fucking fruitcake?
알아들어, 쑥맥아!
Come on, buddy.
어서 가자
He's a great kid.
Yeah, he is.
- 넌 아들 잘 키웠다
- 그럼요
Hello?
저 왔어요
왔니?
Hey!
연락도 없이?
어서 와라
We didn't expect
to see you. Come on in.
- 배고프지?
- 네
Hi. You hungry?
Yeah.
같이 먹자
There's plenty of food.
- 안녕
Hey.
- 머리 멋지다, 제이크
- 고마워요, 새엄마
I like your hair, Jakey.
Thank you.
You look handsome
with a little hair.
Thank you.
- 머리가 짧으니까 더 멋진 걸
- 고마워요
What's going on
with the job?
Lot of sales. Really busy.
- 일은 잘 다니고?
- 그럼요, 바빠요
Just, everything's going
really great.
열심히 하죠
- 어머니는?
- 잘 지내세요
How's your mother?
Wonderful, thank you.
안부 전해 주렴
Tell her I said hello.
I'll do...
- 애인 완다는?
- 잘 지내요
And Wanda?
She's fine.
잠깐 얘기 좀...
Could I talk to you
for a second?
그래
Yeah, sure.
Excuse us.
- 잠시 실례해요
- 잠시만...
Excuse us.
I need to borrow money.
돈 좀 빌려 주세요
I thought we talked
about this.
돈 얘기는 더 이상
안 하기로 했을 텐데
그래요
Yeah.
- 지난 번 거나 갚지
- 죄송해요
You haven't paid me back
for the last time.
I know. I'm sorry. I...
돈이 문제가 아니잖니
It's not the money.
You know that,
don't you, Son?
사고 치고, 돈 빌리고
언제 철 들래?
I just can't keep
bailing you out all the time.
알아요, 딱 한 번만...
I know, man!
I mean, do you...
그깟 몇 푼 빌릴 데
없는 줄 알아요?
Do you think I'd fucking
be here if this wasn't
the last stop on earth?
How much?
얼마냐?
800 bucks.
8백 달러요
Hey.
What's going on?
Jake wants to borrow money.
- 무슨 일이야?
- 돈 빌려 달래
언제까지 이럴 거야?
How many times are we
going to do this, Butch?
자식 놈 마약 살
돈이나 대주고
Kid comes in here
stoned out of his mind,
and you keep throwing money
at him because you don't
want to deal with it.
일도 하니까
I'm working! I have a job.
- 돈 벌어서 꼭 갚을게요
- 아니
I'll pay you back.
No.
이제 안 되겠다
No, I can't do it, Son.
못난 자식 신경 끄고
식사나 하시죠
Right. Sorry to interrupt.
Go back to your
perfect little family.
- 왜 이러니?
- 손대지 마요!
That's not fair.
Don't fucking touch me!
형 집에 놀러 가면 안 돼?
Hey. Can I come with you?
오늘밤엔 좀 바빠
No, kid, not tonight.
I got some shit to do.
알았어
Okay.
그래...
Yeah.
- 괜찮아?
- 응
You okay? You all right?
Yeah.
- 나중에 연락하자
- 알았어
Okay, well, page me later.
Yeah. Yeah.
Okay.
I love you.
Yeah.
- 사랑한다
- 나도
Yeah.
(ALL CHATTERING)
(GUN FIRING)
쪼다자식
계집애처럼 놀래!
Punk-ass bitches.
(LAUGHING)
저 자식들 진짜 멋진데
Look at these
fucking wannabe motherfuckers
진짜 총 쏘면 어떨까?
기분 죽이겠지!
with their fucking guns
and their fucking gold chains.
저것들 진짜 쏘라면 못할 걸
They got nothing!
They're worthless!
저건 그냥
뮤직비디오일 뿐이라구
The only thing these
motherfuckers are shooting
are music videos, dawg.
That's what I'm saying.
- 당연하지
- 저거 다 가짜야!
That's what
I've been saying all along.
- 내 말이
- 맞다니까
That's what
I'm talking about.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
- Now I'm feeling it.
느낌이 오는데?
느낌이 와
슬슬 달아 오른다
Now I'm feeling it, bitches.
You don't want that shit.
No!
가짜 총 필요 없어
뜨거운 걸 보여 주마!
You don't want that shit.
좋았어, 엘비스
BOBBY: Go, Elvis!
춤 춰!
Dance, bitch!
TIKO: You want to call me out?
You want to call me out? Okay.
나랑 붙어 볼래?
Yeah, I want to call you out.
그래
I want to call you out.
- 좋아, 어디 붙어봐!
- 나랑 붙어 봐
- 정말 죽이는데!
- 성병 걸린 놈인데!
MAN 1: Oh, that is so nasty!
MAN 2: Hey, you know
he has herpes, right?
스트립쇼!
Bring it on!
벌써 뿅 간다
I'm fucking high, dawg.
사방이 흔들려!
I can't even... I can't even
see you right now.
TIKO: You ain't shit, Elvis!
Go back to your shelf.
Yeah, dance, bitch.
He's so fucking
brain-dead.
Rape her more!
겁탈해!
Oh, shit!
Come here.
(ALL CHEERING)
맥주 어딨지?
I need a fucking beer.
맥주 좀 갖고 오시지
Hey, would you
get me a cerveza?
맥주?
알았어 내가 가져 올게
ELVIS: Oh, you need a beer,
Johnny?
I'll get you a beer.
내가 갖고 올게, 안젤라
Don't worry about it, Angie.
I got it. I got it. I got it.
내가 갈게, 조니
Yo, I got it, Johnny.
Run, bitch.
Bitch, we're fucking thirsty.
- 잽싸게!
- 목말라 죽겠어
Look at
that slave-ass motherfucker.
"I got it, Johnny."
조니 떠받드는 꼴하곤!
"내가 갈게, 조니"
He's like a spook, man.
- 완전 몸종이야
- 조니 좋아하잖아
TIKO: He loves Johnny.
내 말 맞지, 엘비스?
Yes, he does.
Don't you, Elvis?
- 뭐가?
- 너 조니 사랑하잖아
What?
You love him,
motherfucker. Johnny?
좋아 죽지
Yeah, I do.
I love him a lot.
(ALL LAUGHING)
신세를 많이 져서
I owe him a lot. I do.
시침 떼기는!
No, no, no.
I don't mean like that.
온몸 바쳐 사랑하는
애인이잖아!
I mean you fucking love him.
조니를 위해서라면
뭐든 다 하지
You'd fucking do
anything for him.
If he asked you
to suck his cock,
you probably would.
쟤가 원하면
뿅 가게 화끈 뒹굴어 줄 걸
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
Shut the fuck up.
입 닥쳐
No, no, no.
Tell the truth, Elvis.
빼지 말고 까봐, 엘비스
Tell me you wouldn't drop
to your fucking knees
조니가 원한다면
2초도 안 돼서
무릎 꿇고
물고 빨고 다 할걸!
and suck Johnny's cock
in two seconds,
if he asked you.
거시기에 뽀뽀도 할 거지?
You'd give it a kiss
on the tip. I bet
you would, motherfucker.
- 아니
- 못 해?
No, I wouldn't.
You wouldn't?
Johnny, come on, man.
조니, 왜 이래?
저거 봤어?
Oh, you see that?
'마우스 투 거시기'
챔피언이잖아
Dude, you are
a fucking full-on
'마우스 투 거시기'
챔피언이잖아
dick-in-the-mouth,
balls-across-the-nose,
dildo-up-the-ass...
호모!
Fag!
You're a faggot, dude.
100 percent.
You're a fag.
- 남자한테 흥분하던데!
- 닥치랬지
JOHNNY: Shut the fuck up,
bitch. Suck my cock.
You know what? Don't talk
to me anymore, okay?
계집애랑 노는 건
심심해서 싫으면서!
I fuck bitches. You're a homo.
Suck my cock.
That's it.
- 짜증난다
- 시끄러
That's fucking mean.
Shut the fuck up!
어서 끈쩍하게 해 봐
Suck my fucking cock.
내 거시기 죽어 있거든
Come on, Schmidt,
I'm dead serious.
어서!
Suck it, bitch.
빼지 말고 해!
Suck my fucking cock.
내가 나갈게
(DOORBELL RINGING)
I got it.
어서!
GIRL: Come on, do it!
누구 왔네
어서 해보라니까
No, I got it, all right?
Suck my cock.
저러다 터뜨릴 거야
Pretty soon it's going
to come out, Elvis.
- 커밍아웃 할 거지?
- 멋진 게이 아저씨
TIKO: Pretty soon you're
going to come out, Elvis.
That you're fucking gay.
What up, Jake?
제이크잖아?
You got to start
calling a motherfucker
before you just show up.
연락을 하고 와야지
시간 개념 없는 꼴하곤
Christ-killers
ain't got no respect.
Yeah.
Can I talk to you
for a minute?
FRANKIE: What's up, Jake?
- 잠깐 얘기 좀
- 어서 와
Oh, shit! Yo, come here, man.
Elvis is just about
to suck a dick.
엘비스가 재밌는 거 한대!
Yeah.
Let's go on in here.
무슨 일이야?
So what's going on, homie?
샌디에고 거래 건 알지?
You know that thing I told you
I was going to take care
for you down in San Diego?
- 그래
- 그게 잘 안 됐어
Yeah.
It's a washout.
무슨 일이야?
Really? What happened?
죽도록 쪼고
협박도 했는데
Well, I go down there
and I put the screws to him.
And I tell him, something bad
is gonna happen to him,
돈을 못 주는 거야
unless he comes up
with your money,
and, like, fast.
그 자식 쪽박 차는 바람에
Which he doesn't,
because he's fucking tapped.
But he's scared,
so he leans on his neighbor,
할 수 없이
물건을 빼앗아 왔는데
and I walk on the guy
for 150 bombs.
So?
그래서?
So, the bombs are no good.
The X was fucking bunk.
그게 다 허접인 거야
그걸 팔아서
돈 갚으려고 했는데
And I had a guy lined up
to take it all, man.
We would have made
so much money on that shit.
돈은 안 갚고
뭔 개소리야?
But you said that you would
take care of it. You said
that it was your debt.
구질구질 변명하러 왔냐?
Are you coming in here,
trying to nigger-talk me?
- 뭐 하러 온 거야?
- 물건 개판이라고 말하고
What do you want me to do?
I can't exactly go back
to the guy that I ripped off
그 자식 족쳐야지
and say, "Yo dude,
your shit was no good."
돈이나 갚아
Okay, well,
I still got to get paid.
진정하고
800 달러만 받아
I know. Calm the fuck down.
I got $800.
나눠서 갚을게
And I thought
that we could split it.
You thought
we could split it?
나한테 장난 하냐?
Fuck that.
Pay me all of it.
한 번에 갚아
I'm trying.
How?
- 노력 중이야
- 어떻게?
You make dog shit
at your fucking job.
코딱지만큼 벌어서
언제 갚냐고!
Be careful, Johnny.
I'm not fucking Elvis.
- 난 네 몸종 아니다
- 거지자식!
Yeah, well,
you're short, asshole.
키는 쥐톨만한 게
주둥아리 조심해
Watch your fucking mouth,
you little fucking midget.
난 니 호모 친구들
아니거든
I'm not one of
your little faggot friends.
만만하게 보지 마!
And remember
who you're talking to.
내 돈 내놔
Give me
my fucking money!
날 죽일 거야?
You're going
to stiff me, huh?
죽여 버리겠어!
I'm going
to fucking kill you!
(SCREAMS)
JAKE: Take a fucking drink,
you motherfucker.
물 맛 좀 봐라!
Why don't you fucking die?
죽고 싶냐?
I'm going to kill you,
you fucking bitch!
죽여 버리겠어 개자식!
(DOGS BARKING)
- 그 자식 손대지 마!
- 떨어져!
Take your fucking hands
off him!
Get back!
개자식!
You motherfucker!
프랭키, 계집애 끌고 가
Oh, fuck, Frankie.
Get this fucking bitch
off me.
- 미친 새끼!
- 저 년 좀 데려가!
Fucking psycho, man.
Get the fuck off, bitch!
Who do you think
you're messing with,
you fucking cocksucker?
너 지금 누구한테
개기는 거야?
Get away from me.
이거 놔!
Sit the fuck down,
you crazy bitch!
돌대가리 계집애!
Piece of shit.
Whoa, goddamn it, man!
All right, motherfucker!
- 젠장
- 저 자식 죽여 버리겠어!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Come on, man.
어디 한 번 쏴보시지?
You point that thing at me,
you better pull
the fucking trigger!
겁나서 못 하지?
쪼다 같은 놈!
Well, come on,
you fucking pussy, do it!
Come on, bitch!
(SCREAMING)
쏘라면 못 쏠 줄 알아!
Why don't you try me,
you fucking kike?
- 맘대로 해 봐!
- 죽여주지!
I will! I will!
I love it.
딴 사람은 몰라도
나는 못 속인다
You have everyone else
fooled around here,
but I ain't fucking buying it.
미친 개자식 당장 끌어내
Get this fucking
piece of shit
out of my house.
꺼져
Get the fuck out, dawg!
All right, Johnny.
좋아, 해보자
It's on.
Ain't no turning back now.
언젠가 후회할 거다
Get the fuck
out of here!
꺼지랬지!
Fucking walk away, okay?
꺼져
가자
Come on.
Whoa!
미치겠군
Fuck me.
(MOANING)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
닥쳐 봐
Bitch, shut up.
What's going on?
왜 그래?
Who's there?
It's Zack.
- 누구야?
- 형, 나야
Who? It's fucking midnight!
It's me, Zack.
- 이 오밤중에?
- 나라고
어서 와
Get in here.
What are you doing,
you fucking maniac?
이 시간에, 미쳤냐?
- 안녕
- 안녕하세요
Hi! Hi!
넌 옷이나 입어
내 동생 왔잖아
Okay.
Go put on some clothes.
My brother's here.
그럽죠!
Heil! Yes, sir!
You want a drink?
Yeah.
- 한잔 할래?
- 좋지
엄마 잔소리 땜에
못 살겠어
And she's always
telling me what to do.
옷은 뭘 입어라
어떤 애가 예쁘다...
Like what clothes to wear
and what girls
she thinks are pretty.
내 스스로
할 수 있는 것들 말이야
Like I couldn't fucking
figure it out for myself!
너희 엄마 원래 그렇잖아
That's your mom.
That's Olivia.
널 사랑하시니까
Come on, she loves you.
You're her baby.
알지만 짜증나
Yeah, I know.
It's embarrassing.
Do you know that
we have homework parties?
숙제까지 같이
하려고 든다니까!
What?
Homework parties
with little hats.
- 어떻게?
- 모자까지 쓰신다니까
No.
Yeah.
Like...
그러니까... 생일 파티처럼?
Yeah.
...for birthdays?
그래요
Yeah! Yeah!
그 뿐 아냐...
Another thing.
내가 잠잘 때면...
I'll be sleeping, right?
나를 지긋이
내려다보는 거야
And she'll wake me up
by looking at me.
눈 뜨면
내 방에 들어와 있고
Like I'll open my eyes,
and she'll be right there
looking at me, like...
젠장
Fucking A!
It's goddamn creepy, you know.
Like she's in love with me,
and breathing on me!
엄마는 나 없으면
못 살 것 같다니까!
You're lucky, you know that.
복 받은 줄 알아
I mean, my mother,
she'd never...
우리 엄만 관심도 없었어
맘껏 비웃어라
Boo-hoo for me!
형이 뭐라고 해도
난 형이 부러워
Yeah, I know.
But, you know,
I'd trade you.
집 나오고 싶어
I just got to get out.
취했다, 담배 피울래
Wow, I'm drunk.
I got to smoke.
이런...
Well.
이 녀석 보게, 다 컸네!
Look at Zacky! All grown up!
쭉 빨아봐
스트레스 해소에 짱이야
Look at his little one-hitter
and his stress weed.
Shut up.
됐어
한잔 해
Take a drink.
제대로 해라
Like a pro.
Wacky Zacky.
괴짜 잭!
That's me.
맞아, 난 괴짜야
Wacky Zacky.
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
- 여보세요
- 완다, 잭 바꿔라
Hello?
OLIVIA: Wanda, put my kid
on the phone. Now.
잠시 만요
One minute.
- 너희 엄마야
- 죽어도 싫어!
It's Olivia.
No, no. Fucking A!
좋아
All right, give it to me.
여보세요
Hello?
Zack was supposed to be home
two hours ago. Is he with you?
귀가 시간 두 시간 지났다
형이랑 있니?
Yeah, he's here.
Fucking A, dude.
- 여기 있어요
- 미치겠다
No, we're talking.
얘기 중인데
I said we're talking.
Put him on the phone...
- 얘기중이라고요
- 당장 바꿔
걱정 마세요
제가 데려다 줄게요
Don't get your panties
all in a wad, Olivia.
I'll drive him home later.
지금 몇 신지 알아?
Do you know what time it is?
물론 알죠
알았다니까요
Yes, I do know
what time it is, thank you.
당장 안 바꿔주면
내가 거기로 간다
Put my son on the phone
or I am coming over there
right now, God damn it.
네
Yeah, okay.
알았어요
Yeah, okay. All right!
집에 가야겠다
You got to go home.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
ZACK: No!
WANDA: Wait, no, stop!
- 싫어
- 잠깐만!
JAKE: Come on, Zack!
Tonight we ride!
오늘밤 달려볼까나!
(ZACK LAUGHING)
- 나와
- 싫어!
Come on.
No!
- 나 형 동생 맞지?
- 당연하지
ZACK: Jake. Hey, Jake.
Jake, am I a funny guy?
You're hysterical.
- 나 착하지?
- 최고지
Am I a good guy?
You're the best.
세상에서 최고 착한 놈
Yeah?
Yeah, you are a good guy.
- 형도 최고야
- 이런
You are the best, man.
Oh, boy.
- 들어가
- 아빠
Get inside.
Oh, Dad!
배달 완료요!
You wanted him,
you got him.
Hi!
안녕하세요
Bye!
좋은 밤!
BUTCH: You're a real
son of a bitch,
you know that?
정신 나간 놈!
Come on!
가자!
MAN: I was fucking my dog
one time, right?
No, no, no. Hey...
쟤 엉덩이 좀 봐
Hey, look at the caboose
on that one.
I could crack that open
like a peach.
저 여자랑 한 번 해볼까?
Are you fucking kidding me?
노인네가
망령이라도 나셨나?
You are a fucking dinosaur,
Cosmo.
노인네가
망령이라도 나셨나?
거기 탄력 떨어진 게
언젠데!
Come on. You're dead.
You can't do anything.
- 쭈글쭈글 할 걸!
- 뭐라고?
Your balls
are all wrinkled up.
What?
기운 떨어진 노땅이잖아!
"What?" You deaf fuck.
I said you're old.
내 실력 몰라주네
I can knock the bottom
out of her.
- 방향도 못 잡으면서
- 나 쑥쑥 잘해
You don't even know
what a bottom is.
You don't know what to do.
Balls deep.
이봐, 완다!
Hey, waitress!
- 뭐 더 필요해?
- 자기도 하고 싶지?
What can I do for you?
What did you have in mind?
Just get another
round of drinks.
술 더 가져와
You haven't finished
the last ones.
I didn't ask you that.
- 많이 남았잖아!
- 말대답 말아
- 술이나 더 가져와
- 이게 건방지게!
Just get us some more
fucking drinks.
Get us some drinks, bitch!
왜 그러니?
Come on.
Mind your manners.
그만 하자, 계산서
We're fine.
Just give me the bill.
아뇨, 내가 낼게요
Hey, no, Dad.
Come on, I got it.
네가 낸다고?
떼돈 버냐?
Oh, you got it, huh?
What are you...
Look at this guy.
- 그럴 일이 있어요
- 확실히 쏘네!
Special occasion.
Big spender over here!
- 모두 나가요
- 조니가 나가래요
Come on, Cos, let's go.
Johnny says
we're leaving, let's go!
Hey, Johnny,
watch this.
Tell Jake we stopped in.
Oh, I will.
- 제이크한테 안부 전해
- 그럴게
니 남친에게 내라고 해
이년아
그 일을 말했더니
제이크가 난리를 쳐서
When I told Jake
what happened,
he fucking flipped out.
진정시켜야 했어요
And I had to calm him down.
조니를 죽이겠다고 광분했죠
He was going to kill Johnny.
제이크는 성질이
아주 급하거든요
Jake's like that.
He's a very passionate
person.
완다 헤인즈
그래서 내가 충고해줬어요
But I told him,
"No. If you're gonna
do something,
복수하려면 그의 약점을
먼저 잡으라고
"you got to fucking
hit him where it hurts."
조니가 차를 도둑맞은 척 하고
Johnny had a car stolen
by a mutual acquaintance,
보험금을 타려고 했는데
and he was trying to collect
on the insurance money.
바비 케이
일명 911
Jake comes in,
salts the whole fucking deal,
제이크가 그걸 다
꼬지른 거예요
insurance company
catches wind of it,
결국 조니는 보험회사에서
개망신 당했고
they don't pay out.
3만 달러나 손해 봤으니
Costs Johnny $30,000.
조니 성질에
가만 못 있죠
Of course,
Johnny had to retaliate.
It's fucking business.
Mr. Johansson
wants to see you.
E.W. 텔레마케팅 사: 포모나, 캘리포니아
사장님이 불러
부르셨어요?
You wanted to see me?
앉게
Sit down.
What's up, Pete?
무슨 일로?
Your probation officer called.
보호관찰관이 왔었네
You talked to Mr. Lampington?
I thought he was out of town.
그 아저씨?
출장 갔을 텐데
Yeah. Well,
I talked to him.
하여간 만났네
He says you've been getting
into trouble again.
자네 또 말썽이라고 하던데
빈집 들어가 마약 한다고
Breaking into houses,
using drugs. Speed, mainly.
- 아니에요
- 사실이잖아
It's not true.
Yeah, it is.
No, it's not.
하늘에 맹세코
그런 짓 안 했어요
Pete, I swear to God.
이봐요, 이봐...
Dude. Dude! It's...
나도 알아요...
I feel you. I'm right here.
벌레 보듯이 하지 말아요!
사실을 말하고 있다구요
Don't look at me that way.
I'm telling you
the fucking truth!
하늘에 맹세코
마약 안 했어요!
I'm totally
fucking straight, man!
I mean, I'm a little...
다만 난...
Mr. Lampington
is so full of shit.
He's out of fucking town.
보호관찰관은
여기 있지도 않은데
How would he know
what I'm doing?
어떤 미친놈이 그런
개소리를 한 거야!
You disappoint me.
Pete.
- 너 같은 걸 믿다니
- 사장님
사장님...
Pete.
- 제발 믿어 주세요
- 소변 검사해
I swear to fucking God.
I need you
to take a drug test.
나 쫓겨나면 안 돼요!
Pete, come on.
I need this job.
- 돈이 필요해요!
- 소변 받아와
I really need this job.
Fill it up.
쫓겨나면 안 된다구요
I need this fucking job!
젠장!
Back off!
젠장! 나가!
Fuck you! Fuck you!
Fuck you!
Get the fuck out of here!
You're fired!
넌 해고야
얼씬도 하지 마
Get your shit and get out!
Do not let him back in here!
당장 꺼져
여기 발도 못 붙이게 해!
I will take you down
to hell with me!
내가 지옥 가면
혼자 갈 줄 알아?
Get the fuck out of here!
당장 꺼져!
너희들 다 꼬챙이에
꿰서 갈 거야!
I will take you down
to fucking hell with me!
나 혼자만
당하진 않을 거라구!
I will take you down
to hell with me!
(MUSIC BLARING)
(MEN WHOOPING)
이런 걸 원한 거냐, 조니?
맞장 떠보자!
You want to play some games,
Truelove? Let's play
some motherfucking games.
(DOGS BARKING)
당장 못 나와?
Motherfucker. Fuck that!
이 새끼 어디 있어?
JAKE: Where's
this motherfucker?
Where you at? Johnny?
어디 숨은 거야?
Johnny!
MAN: Go check the bathroom.
- 조니!
- 화장실 뒤져 봐!
Johnny!
조니?
제이크!
Jake!
Truelove!
트루 러브!
- TV 완전 죽인다!
- 그거 업어 가
Oh, shit,
look at this fucking TV!
Fuck the TV.
개새끼는 왜 저렇게 짖어?
Shut the fuck up!
Shoot the fucking...
Fuck the motherfucking dog,
man.
(JAKE GRUNTING)
MAN 1: The bitch ain't here,
man. Let's get out of here.
그 자식 여기 없는 것 같아
어서 나가자!
What the fuck
are you doing, man?
제이크, 뭘 처먹고
똥까지 싸냐?
What the fuck
did you eat, bro?
네 똥 밟을라
MAN 2: Be careful,
don't step on your own shit.
이 TV 진짜 무겁다
Oh, man, this fucker's
real heavy. Shit.
절대 떨어뜨리지 마
No, don't drop it. Wait.
Don't fucking drop it.
MAN 1: Yo, I'm keeping
this motherfucking TV.
이 TV는 내가 챙긴다
Don't fuck with it.
Don't fuck with it,
all right?
망가지지 않게 잘 다뤄
You ready or what?
MAN 2: Let's go, come on.
- 준비 됐어?
- 어서 가자!
- 어서 뜨자니까!
- 출발!
Let's get the fuck
out of here.
Let's go!
축제 갈 거지?
어서 가자!
Fiesta, motherfuckers,
we ready?
뭐 하는 거야?
Yo, what the fuck, dude?
We're moving, bro.
여기 뜰 거야
Moving?
Goddamn right.
- 이사 가?
- 그래
It's too fucking hot.
Too many assholes
know where I live.
쓰레기 같은 것들이
몰려와서 못 살겠어
You see this?
이것 좀 봐!
개판이네!
Holy shit!
조니, 어떻게 된 거야?
Yo, Johnny,
what happened, man?
어제 집에 왔더니
I come home last night.
누가 창문 박살내고
TV 훔쳐갔어
My window was busted
and my TV is missing.
- 진짜야
- 재수 없어!
Fuck, right?
Fuck!
- 똥까지 쌌어
- 똥?
Tell him about the shit.
The shit?
제이크가 약에 쩔어서
카펫에다 그 짓까지 했어
Fucking crackhead Mazursky
took a sideways shit
on the living room carpet.
- 어디?
- 바로 여기
What? Where?
Right here.
On the wet spot.
축축하잖아
A big fucking steaming crap.
그것도 커다랗고
길쭉하게 뽑아놨다니까!
Longways, like this, dawg.
That's fucked up.
Is that nuts or what?
- 기분 엿 같겠다
- 그 자식 완전 또라이 아냐?
근데 거긴 손으로 닦았나?
What this motherfucker
wipe his ass with? His hand?
난 집에 없었으니
모르지
I don't know, fucko.
I told you I wasn't here.
하여간 생긴 대로 놀아!
Whatever. That fool
is fucking nasty, man.
전화녹음 들어 봐
Check this shit out.
일요일 오전 12시...
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Sunday, 12:00 a.m.
너무 겁먹지 마라
겨우 시작이거든
JAKE: This is just
the beginning, bitch.
This is Li'I Shooter.
넌 죽은 목숨이야
이 난쟁이 같은 자식아
You're dead, homes.
You hear me,
you fucking dwarf?
니 에미 사는 곳도 알고
I know where
your mother lives.
I know
where your brother lives.
I know where your papi lives.
동생이랑 꼰대
사는 곳도 알거든?
We going to play some games,
motherfucker!
다들 무사하지 못할 거다
Mazursky, right?
Can you believe that shit?
- 제이크잖아!
- 이럴 수가 있니?
은혜를 원수로 갚다니!
After everything I've done
for that motherfucker?
똥밟은 셈 쳐!
Look, Johnny, fuck him.
축제 가서
계집애들이나 꼬시자
Let's get the hell
out of Dodge. Go to Fiesta.
Fuck some bitches.
- 내 말이!
- 그래
That's what I'm talking about.
Right?
질펀하게 놀아보자고!
Let's run through some shit!
우리 놀고 올 동안
넌 똥치우고 청소나 해
Schmitty, we're going
to go to the Springs
for a couple days.
You stay here
and get everything
all boxed up and out.
돌아와서 이런 꼴
또 보지 않게
I don't want to see shit here
when I get back, okay?
- 알았어
- 영수증도 챙겨줘
All right.
I want a receipt, too.
Yeah, and maybe
if you guys are still there
when I get finished,
일 끝낼 때 까지
너희들 거기 있을까?
I'll cruise down there.
나도 가도 되지?
Yeah. Maybe you can blow me.
Fuck you, dick.
I wanna come.
- 몸 바쳐 봉사할 거면 오고
- 빌어먹을, 나도 가고 싶다고
거실 똥이나 치워!
살살이 자식!
Yeah, yeah. Just make sure
you get the shit smell
out of the carpet, bitch!
뭘 어쩌려고?
I don't get it.
What are we doing?
자식 머리통을
뽀개버릴 거야
Let's go break
this fucking guy's head.
Mazursky!
제이크!
없나봐
He's not here.
튄 거야, 차도 없잖아
I'm telling you,
he's gone, man. Look,
his car is not even here.
가만 있어봐
That don't mean shit.
불도 꺼져 있잖아!
There's not even
any fucking lights on.
벌건 대낮에 어떤
미친놈이 불을 켜냐?
How are the lights going
to be on? It's the middle
of the fucking day.
What the fuck are we doing?
우리만 쪼다 됐네!
I don't know,
but I'm not standing here
like a fucking idiot.
얼뜨기처럼 이게 뭐냐?
- 뭐 하냐?
- 그냥 장난이야
What are you doing?
I'm just kidding.
그만 좀 해
All right,
so quit fucking around.
조니, 이거 봐!
Hey! Yo, J!
Check it out.
시속 160이다
이 개자식아!
97 miles an hour,
motherfucker!
- 너도 해봐
- 챔피언 나가신다!
Okay.
Let's see what you got.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Manny motherfucking Ramirez,
motherfucker!
개자식, 가만 안 둔다!
You guys are fucking idiots.
덜 떨어진 것들!
(BUTCH AND OLIVIA CHATTERING)
시끄러워서
잠을 못 자겠네
Jesus! Make more noise.
잭은 겨우 15살이야
He's 15. You remember
when you were 15?
테니스 약속 늦어서
이러시는군
You know what?
For once in your life,
your tennis match will wait.
아빠가 그런 말도 못 해?
Why do you have to be such
a fucking pussy?
What are you thinking?
What are you
getting crazy about?
제발 진정해!
It's not that big a deal.
I am not crazy!
- 별것도 아닌 것 갖고
- 애한테 관심 좀 가져봐!
If you were ever here...
Would you just leave it?
...you might notice that.
Oh, great. Let's just
let him turn out like...
Like what, Olivia? Like who?
- 잭까지 그 놈처럼 만들 거야?
- 그 놈이라니?
Like what?
Say it. Like Jake?
- 누구냐고?
- 제이크 말이야?
엄마, 아빠
무슨 일이에요?
Hey.
What's going on?
이런...
Oh, jeez.
이리 와라
BUTCH: Come here.
이리 와
Come here.
엄마가 네 방에서
이걸 찾아냈다
Your mother found this
in your room.
It's a pipe.
I know what it is.
It's a bong.
- 파이프네요
- 마리화나용 파이프지
You want to tell me about it?
No.
- 이거 보고 할 말 없니?
- 아뇨
You smoking pot?
No.
- 마약하니?
- 아뇨
Now, look at me!
We have to talk, Son.
- 내 눈 보고 말해!
- 할 말 없어요
I don't want
to fucking talk, Dad.
Well, that's too bad.
Sit down.
와서 앉아 봐
Dad! I just fucking woke up!
방금 일어났잖아요
젠장, 옷부터 입고요
Goddamn it!
Let me put some
fucking clothes on.
아침부터 재수 없어!
God! Fucking dick!
1일 째, 1999년 11월 6일 금요일
오전 9시 48분
외출금지 시켜던지
무슨 조치를 취해야 해
OLIVIA: Yes, he should be
grounded. He should be
something, for God's sake!
Zack, come down here!
잭, 어서 내려와!
Zack?
잭?
카훌라 공원
오전 10시 17분
Are you fucking kidding me?
What?
이게 웬 떡이냐?
그 놈 동생이잖아, 세워
That's Tattooey's brother.
Pull over.
Hey, what's up?
Come here.
- 거기 서!
- 가만 있어!
거기 서, 이 자식아!
Come here,
you little fucker.
네가 도망가면
살 거 같아!
What the fuck
you running for, bitch?
조안나 커쉬너
증인 1
데일 디에커
증인 2
- 가자
- 어서
Let's go, let's go.
Come on.
날 어쩌려고?
난 아무 짓도 안했어
Dude,
what the fuck are you doing?
I didn't fucking do anything.
닥치고 차에 타!
Shut the fuck up
and get in the fucking van!
이 돌대가리!
Fucking idiot.
너희 집에 데려가
Just take him to your place.
아버지한테 뭐라고 하고?
We can't take him to my place.
I told you, my dad's there.
아버지 다 이해한다며?
I thought you said
he was cool.
그렇다고 애 납치한 걸
가만 두겠냐?
Bitch, he is cool.
But you didn't tell me
we'd be bringing along
a fucking hostage!
납치 아니거든
Dude, he's not a hostage,
all right?
I told you, I don't know
what I'm doing right now,
all right.
어떻게 할지
나도 잘 모르겠다
팜 스프링스, 캘리포니아: 오후 3시 16분
- 생각 좀 해보고
- 그럼 생각해
I'm thinking.
Well, think.
Well... Hey,
we got to take him someplace.
어디든 데려가야 돼
한 군데 있긴 한데
얌전하게 굴어야 돼
All right.
I know somewhere we can go.
But you got to be
fucking cool.
처키 모타의 아파트
오후 3시 32분
(TV CHATTERING)
- 누구세요?
- 나야
CHUCKY: Yeah?
Yo!
웬 일이야?
Hey, what's up, man?
- 잘 지내요, 처키?
- 잘 지냈어?
What's up, Chucky?
What's up, bro?
Lot of dudes, bro.
I know, man.
- 떼거지로 왔네
- 그렇게 됐어요
All right. Bring them in.
들어와
Hey, Chuck, this is Truelove,
the guy I was
telling you about.
지난번에 말한
내 친구 조니
- 반가워
- 방 남는 거 있어요?
Hey, what's up, man?
Do you have a room
we could use?
- 방?
- 네
A room?
Yeah.
왼쪽 끝방 비었어
Yeah, I got one
all the way down to the left.
고마워
Thanks.
So, what's up, man?
별일 없죠?
You know,
we're just chilling, man.
곧 큰 파티잖아
Getting high.
Getting ready to go to Fiesta.
Smoking weed.
- 미리 기분 좀 냈지
- 마리화나도 피우고
Thanks, man.
고마워요
요즘 어떻게 지내요?
So, how you been?
잘 지내
서핑하고 빈둥대고
Been good. Chilling.
Ripping waves. Hanging out.
(ZACK SHOUTING)
쟤네들 뭐하는 거냐?
Yo! What the fuck is going on
back there, man?
가볼까요?
Do you want me
to go check it out?
생판 처음 본 놈들이
무슨 수작이야?
Yeah. I mean,
four dudes I've never met
are in my fucking bedroom.
Yeah.
선샤인 파슨스 처키 모타
샤니아 로페즈: 증인 3, 4, 5
- 여기 좀 도와줘
- 테이프 줘
MAN: Give me your hands.
JOHNNY: Give me the tape.
Whoa! What the fuck
are you doing, man?
무슨 짓이야?
Are you nuts?
You can't do that!
게이 럼피 예거: 증인 6
완전 돌았구나!
- 너희 제정신이야?
- 어머나, 이게 뭐니?
You guys are out
of your fucking mind.
What the hell is this?
- 넌 누구야?
- 닥쳐
Who the fuck are you?
Shut up.
얘들이 꼬맹이를 묶고 있어
Hey, Chucky,
they got a kid tied up
in your bedroom!
- 진정해
- 저기 애가 있어
Hey, calm down.
There's a kid!
- 뭐?
- 그런게 아니에요
What?
It's not like that.
- 조니가 홧김에 그만
- 뭐가 어째?
Johnny's just a little crazy
right now.
A little crazy right now?
- 얘를 납치하긴 했는데...
- 뭐?
We stole this kid...
What?
- 어떻게 할지...
- 이봐!
I don't know...
Hey!
닥치라고 했을 텐데
I thought I told you
to shut your mouth.
주제넘게 참견 말라고
And you
mind your fucking business.
Mind my business?
This is my fucking house!
너야말로 남의 집에서
뭔 개수작이야!
Frankie, you better put
your boy in check. Tell them
what fucking time it is.
프랭키, 설명해
난 골 아프다
Oh, it's like that, huh?
Just like that, bitch.
- 감 잡았다
- 그럼 됐네
I get it. Yo, Lump,
let's get out of here.
너희들 당장 나가
난 축제 갈거니까
돌아오기 전에 다 꺼져
Yo! I'm going
to fucking Fiesta.
And when I get back,
none of you motherfuckers
better be here.
모두 가자, 어서
Let's get out of here, girls.
Lump, let's go.
- 젠장!
- 재수가 없으려니!
Fuck.
Fucking shitheads.
처키, 정말 미안해요
Hey, Chucky, man,
I'm really sorry
about all this, bro.
Fuck!
엿 같군!
(TV CHATTERING)
왜 이래? 떠야지?
What's going on?
Why aren't you guys ready?
- 그럼 얘는 어떻게 하고?
- 아무렴 어때!
What are we going to do
with the kid, man?
Who cares?
벽장에 처넣든가
차 안에 처박든지
Throw him in the fucking
closet. Pick him up later.
Leave him in the van.
멋대로 해
I don't give a fuck.
조니, 난 돌아가야 돼
Hey, yo, Johnny.
I got a date
back in the Valley.
애인이 기다려
I got to get back, man.
나도
Me, too.
You just remembered now, huh?
갑자기 왜들 이래?
Yeah.
Yeah, man.
- 알잖아
- 그래
Hey, my girl gets mad
if I don't fuck her.
섹스 안 해주면
애인이 화내거든
You pussies want to go home?
Fine. Take the fucking van.
꺼져, 겁쟁이들아
차 갖고 꺼져!
그냥 옷장에 가둬 놔
도망 안 갈게
Listen. You don't
have to do that,
you know.
I mean, you can put me
in a closet.
I'm not gonna run anywhere.
넌 입 나불대면
죽여 버린다!
Do me a favor.
Shut up before
I shut you the fuck up.
Johnny.
조니
이 자식 주둥아리
분명 막은 것 같은데
Why is this motherfucker
even talking, anyway?
I thought we taped him up.
숨 못 쉴까봐
He couldn't breathe.
난 축제 거리에
떨궈주고 가
Just drop me off on the strip.
I'm going to fucking Fiesta.
이 자식 땜에
다 망칠 수야 없지
I'm not letting
this little motherfucker
throw my weekend.
He couldn't breathe.
숨을 못 쉴까봐 라니...
What about me?
No.
- 나는?
- 안 돼
No what?
He stays with you.
- 뭐가 안 돼?
- 인질 감시해야지
What?
- 뭐라고?
- 한 번에 알아 들어라
I said,
"All fucking queers are deaf,"
motherfucker.
- 왜 내가?
- 까라면 까야지
Why me, dude?
Because I fucking said so.
일 복잡하게 하지마
Don't fuck around, man.
아버지 때문에
우리집은 안 돼
I can't fucking take him
to my dad's house like that.
도망갈 놈도 아닌데
그냥 데리고 가
Well, then, untie him, genius.
You heard the kid.
He ain't running, are you?
- 뭐라고? 맞아
- 됐지?
What? No.
There you go.
새로 사귄 애인이라고
하면 되잖아
Go home, tell Juergen he's
your new little butt buddy
and he's spending the night.
제이크랑 거래해야지
Meanwhile,
I'll talk to Mazursky.
He must be going crazy
right now.
지금쯤 거품 물었겠다
Hey, what's going on?
- 무슨 일이에요?
- 난리가 났다
It's a madhouse.
네 동생 잭이 사라졌어
Your brother's scaring
the shit out of all of us.
친구네 집은요?
여자 친구는요?
You try his friends?
Maybe he has a girl.
아무 데도 없다
친구네, 경찰서, 병원...
We've tried everything.
Friends, cops, hospitals.
Nothing.
놀러나간 거 아니에요?
You don't think
the kid's just, like,
out fucking around?
집에 언제까지
가둬둘 순 없잖아요
I mean, you can't keep
the kid locked
in the house forever.
뭐가 어떻게 된 건지...
Maybe. I don't know.
We did have an argument
this morning.
아침에 야단 좀 쳤거든
Okay, well, that's what it is,
then, right?
- 집 나간 거군요
- 그럴 지도
I hope so.
Well, what do you think?
I don't know.
- 아빠 생각은요?
- 모르겠다
모든 가능성을
생각해 봐야지
But, we can't
rule anything out, so...
하나 궁금한 게 있는데
I have to ask you
a few questions.
- 좀 물어보자
- 네
Okay?
Okay.
누가 잭을
해치려는 건 아닐까?
You know anybody
who'd want to hurt Zack?
- 설마요
- 너 때문에 말야
No.
You?
- 누가요?
- 너한테 원한 있는 놈
Me what?
You have a beef with anybody
I should know about?
No.
That person you owe money to?
- 없어요
- 너한테 돈 빌려준 놈!
You owe somebody money?
너 돈 꿨니?
Oh, Jesus! You just tell me
how much and I
will write the check.
대체 얼마야?
당장 갚아 줄게
It's not really
like that, Olivia.
Really? What's it like?
- 그런 게 아니에요
- 그럼 뭐야?
다 너 때문이야, 미친놈
Tell me what it's like, you...
Goddamn you! You fuck!
- 잭을 찾아내
- 진정하세요
Get him back here!
Please relax.
당장 구해내!
Get him back here to me.
찾아서 데려와
Bring him back here!
잭을 찾을게요
I'm going to find him,
I promise you.
약속해요
(SOBBING)
I'll find him.
꼭 데려 올게요
BUTCH: Where are you going?
어디 가니?
(MUSIC PLAYING)
개자식 조니 어딨어?
De Rosa! Where's Johnny?
몰라, 여기 있대?
I don't know, dawg.
Is he here?
- 알면 묻겠냐?
- 얘기 중인데
That's what
I'm asking you, "dawg"!
Excuse me, we were talking.
- 조니 일당 어딨어?
- 못 봤는데
Klemash,
where's the fucking crew?
Man, I ain't seen them dudes.
너희들까지
나 무시할 거야?
What the fuck was that?
You give me your back?
You turn away from me?
물러서 이 자식아
Why are you tripping, homes?
Back up, freak-ass!
걔한테 손대지 마
Don't touch her!
You fucking asshole!
이 개또라이!
(SCREAMING)
조니한테
똑똑히 전해라...
If anybody
sees Johnny Truelove,
tell them Jake Mazursky
is looking for him!
제이크가 보자고 한다고
Thank you.
그럼
(ALL YELLING)
(CAR HORN HONKING)
신나게 놀자
BOY: Hey, suck my dick!
축제의 거리
팜 스프링스, 캘리포니아
대단하다!
Dude.
(WOMEN SHOUTING)
그렇게 까불다 죽는다
You better
back the fuck off me, man!
I'm going to get a beer.
You want one?
Yeah, sure.
- 맥주 마실래?
- 좋아
- 받아
- 고마워
Here you go, man.
Thanks.
Cigarette?
No, I don't smoke.
- 담배?
- 안 피워
Fuck that.
It's good for you.
건강에 좋은 걸 왜?
있잖아...
Hey, man,
이러면 어떨까?
저쪽으로 걸어가서
what if I said you could
walk over there right now,
넌 버스 타고
잽싸게 집으로 튀는 거야
jump on a bus,
catch a ride home?
I turn my back, tell Truelove
you fucking ran away
or something.
조니한테는
네가 튀었다고 뻥치고
What do you think about that?
난 모른 척 하는 거지
모르겠어...
I don't know, Frankie.
그랬다가 우리 형이
곤란해질까 봐
I mean, I don't want to cause
any problems for my brother,
you know?
힘들어도 버텨볼게
So, I think, I'm just
going to ride it out,
see what happens.
알았지?
All right?
좋을 대로
All right.
프랭키의 집
오후 11시 48분
Try and
keep it down, okay?
(WOMEN LAUGHING)
아버지!
Dad?
Frankie?
프랭키?
프랭키
Frankie.
유르겐 발렌바커, 데스티니 헤스큐와 친구
증인 7, 8, 9
우리 아들 왔구나
I'm so glad
to see you, bro!
I know.
So glad.
Oh, my beautiful baby!
Come on, Dad, don't do that.
- 우리 귀여운 왕자님
- 제발 이러지 말아요
Hey, come to bed.
이제 그만 자자
사랑해
I love you.
예쁜이들 소개해 줄까?
I want you to meet
this beautiful...
All right, all right,
all right.
알았어요
Nice to meet you.
Yes, hi.
- 반가워요
- 안녕
Give her a kiss.
Be a gentleman.
Dad! Seriously!
- 다 같이 놀아 볼까나?
- 저는 잘게요
Just fucking
join in the fun, man.
FRANKIE:
No, you have fun.
I'm gonna go.
아버지나 재미 보세요
- 저 갈게요
- 파티 막 시작했는데!
Let me go, Dad.
No, stay! The party's
just getting started.
애비랑 한 대 땡기고
Come on, man,
smoke a doobie
with your old man!
- 한 잔 해야지
- 싫어요
Have a drink!
No!
- 이리 와
- 아녜요, 가자
Come on. Something.
No, Dad. Come on.
꼬마는 뭐냐?
베이비시터 하냐?
Who's your little friend?
You babysitting?
주책이야!
Fuck you!
- 소파에서 자
- 알았어
Take the couch.
All right.
- 됐지?
- 응
You good?
Yeah.
2일 째: 1999년 11월 7일 토요일
오전 7시 34분
일어나
Wake up.
할일이 태산인데
아직도 자빠져 자?
Come on, you got
chores to do. Let's go.
- 어서
- 알아요!
Hello?
I fucking hear you!
There's coffee. But Destiny
got up late, so I need you
to straighten up the house.
커피는 내렸으니까
넌 어서 청소해라
I'm supposed to clean up
after your party?
아빠가 실컷 놀고
청소는 나 시켜요?
I'm hung over like a bitch.
Don't argue with me.
I'm in no mood.
술 안 깨서 골 땡겨
시키는 대로 해
집 개판으로 만든 건
바로 너거든
Hey, look, I come home here
yesterday, and your shit's
all over the house!
일자리 못 구해서
여기 살려면 일해야지
We had a deal, remember?
You get a job, you pay rent,
- 아니면 독립하던가
- 알았어요, 젠장
or you work here.
All right! Fuck!
- 당장 나가요
- 말버릇 하고는...
Get out of my room!
Nice fucking mouth.
짱나 죽겠어!
Fucking dick.
걱정 마, 내가 도와 줄게
Hey, don't worry about it.
I'll help you with the work.
아버지는 완전 식물학자야
야채를 다 키워 먹거든
Juergen's a botanist.
He grows everything
we eat right here.
Tomatoes, cucumbers, corn.
토마토, 오이,
옥수수, 온갖 향료에...
Fucking spices and shit.
Motherfucker's
a full-blown alcoholic,
smokes like a chimney,
영감탱이
술, 담배에 쩔어 살면서
but goddamn if we don't
eat healthy, right?
건강식 먹겠다고
쇼를 해요
이게 뭔지 아니?
Oh, yeah.
Look at this shit
right here.
- 이런!
- 아버지의 자부심과 기쁨
Oh, boy!
Daddy's pride and joy.
꼰대가 대마초를
다 피워 버리지
Of course, that greedy bastard
will smoke them all,
근데 내가 다 키워
but it's Frankie's job
to take care of them.
물주고, 잡초 뽑고
계란껍질 뿌리고
Water them, pull the males,
throw a little eggshells
on them, every now and then.
- 대마초를?
- 그래 맞아
Dope.
Yeah, right?
일이나 하자
Well, fuck it.
Let's get to work.
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
- 젠장, 전화 받고 올게
- 알았어
Shit. I'll be right back.
All right.
- 여보세요
- 안녕
Hello.
SUSAN: Hey!
- 안녕, 수잔
- 뭐 해?
Hey, girl.
What's going on?
지금 일하는 중이야
올 거지?
Nothing. Working.
You guys coming over?
- 준비했어?
- 당연히 준비했지
You got that shit?
You know I do.
수잔의 집: 오전 10월 20일
- 엄마, 프랭키 집에 놀러가요
- 얘기된 거야?
Mom, we're going to Frankie's!
Hey, did you talk to him?
그럼
It's all good.
- 언제 오니?
- 늦을 거예요
When will you be home?
I don't know.
Late, probably.
Darling, can you stay with
Julie and Sabrina tonight?
너희 친구네 집에서
자면 안 되니?
It's your father
and my anniversary.
엄마, 아빠
결혼기념일이잖아
Anniversary.
- 기념으로 찐하게 섹스...
- 못 말려
You going to have
a little sex or...
That's disgusting!
재밌잖아
Whatever. I'm interested.
이렇게 해줄 거예요?
I mean, really.
Are you going to
go down on him?
- 재미 좀 볼 거예요?
- 됐다
Give him
a little tubesteak boogie?
No.
결혼한 지 오래됐다고
그 재미까지 버리면 안 되죠
Oh, come on. Live a little.
I mean, you guys
have been married,
what, like, 500 years?
키스, 후려치지 전에
그만 해라!
Keith Stratten!
I will smack
the shit out of you,
you little skunk!
우리 갈게요
All right, okay,
we're leaving.
열쇠 있지?
사브리나랑 줄리한테 가자
You got your keys.
Let's go get
Sabrina and Julie.
Bye.
갈게요
이봐, 꼬맹이
이리 와봐
Hey! Yo! Yo! Youngblood!
Come here, man. Come here.
사브리나 포프, 수잔 하튜니언
줄리 버클리, 증인 10, 11, 12
- 여긴 숙녀분들과 멍청이
- 죽을래?
Ladies. Dickwad.
Fuck you.
- 수잔
- 안녕
Susan.
Hi.
Pleased to meet you.
Sabrina. Julie.
- 만나서 반가워
- 사브리나, 줄리
Dickwad.
Hey, buddy.
Fucking Keith, man.
- 그리고 멍청이
- 반갑다, 키스라고 해
Okay, okay,
let's go smoke
some fucking weed, man!
대마초나 대령해
All right. Yo!
Hey, but listen.
- 좋아
- 잠깐 들어 봐
뼈 빠지게 청소한 거야
더럽히면 죽는다
No!
Nobody mess up
my shit, all right?
This house has never been
so fucking clean.
- 웃기고 있네
- 너 게임 정말 못한다
Fuck you, dude.
You fucking suck
at these games.
- 조용히 해
- 니가 게임 다 망치고 있어
You suck.
You fucking blow
at this game, dude.
죽은 건 너라고
I don't fucking blow.
You just died, man!
- 다른 놈한테 죽었거든
- 그게 내 거야
I thought I was
the other guy.
No, dude, that's me.
- 난 다른 놈이랑 하는 줄 알았어
- 웃기지 마
I thought I was playing
the other dude.
No. Fuck you, dude.
You're fucking high, dude.
완전 또라이구나
Yeah, I'm high.
I'm ruined after
five minutes of this shit.
- 나 잘해
- 5분만에 다 죽었으면서
This shit is creepy
as a motherfucker.
그 놈의 머리는
제대로 돌지를 않아
- 진짜 하수구나
- 아니거든
You're a lightweight, dawg.
I'm not a lightweight.
- 죽여 버린다
- 누가 할 소리
Suck my balls.
Dude, fuck you.
Suck my balls, man!
게임도 못 하는 찌질한 놈
You suck it, bitch.
You fucking wimp.
- 몇 살이야
- 몇 살 같아?
So, how old are you?
How old do I look?
12살?
About 12.
17살인데 좀 어려 보여
Oh, well, I'm 17,
but I do look really young.
- 내가 죽여 줄게
- 누가 할 소릴?
I'm gonna kill your ass.
Answer your phone.
Go. Go answer your phone!
전화 받아
가서 전화나 받으라고!
Suck it! Suck it! Suck it!
No, bitch, fuck you!
- 까불어라
- 멍청이
Shut up!
Fuck you!
- 닥쳐!
- 됐거든
여보세요
조니, 제이크랑 얘기는 잘 됐어?
Hello? Yo, Johnny! What's up?
Have you talked to anybody?
아직이야... 왜?
Not yet. Why?
잭을 계속 둘 순 없어
Look, man. I can't
keep the kid here
much longer.
- 왜?
- 별건 아니고
Why?
Nothing.
누가 좀 와있어
I'm just having
some people over.
- 뭐?
- 조용히 좀 해
What?
Nobody. Shut up!
- 너 미쳤냐?
- 그냥 친구들이야
What? Are you crazy?
Nobody. Just some people.
누가 걔들이랑 노닥거리래?
Dude, I didn't tell you
to play fucking grab-ass!
진정해
Chill out, dawg.
모두 당장 내보내
No, fuck that!
Get everyone
the fuck out of there!
알았어, 가라고 할게
All right. All right.
I'll clear it out.
I need you to do
a favor for me, bro.
부탁 좀 들어줘
Johnny's coming over
and I need the house.
조니가 온다니까
잭 데리고 나가
Will you watch the kid for me
for a little while?
Watch him?
Yeah. Keep an eye on him.
- 나가서 뭐해?
- 그냥 감시만 하면 돼
전화 못하게 하고
혼자 두지 말고
No phones
and no leaving him alone.
전화는 왜 못 하게 해?
No phones?
나 안 할래
I don't get it.
안 떠벌리면 말해 줄게
All right, look. If I tell you
something, can you keep
your fucking mouth shut?
그래, 물론이지
Yeah, of course, man. Yeah.
쟤네 형이 조니한테
돈을 꿨거든
The kid's older brother
owes Truelove money
돈 받을 때까지
잡아두는 거야!
and Johnny's holding him
like a marker or something,
until he gets paid.
That's fucked up.
애 잡겠군
No. No, bitch,
it's not like that.
잭이 말을 잘 들어서
문제없어
The kid knows
what's happening,
and he's cool with it.
봐라, 잘 놀고 있잖아
I mean, look at
the motherfucker.
He ain't going nowhere.
몇 시간 데리고
놀다가 돌아와
Just take him someplace,
hang out, bring him back
in a couple of hours.
할 수 있지?
Can you do that for me?
해야 되나...
I don't know, man.
꿍꿍이를
알 수가 없으니
It sounds
pretty fucking dubious.
키스, 네가 이럼 안 되지
Keith, who the fuck
are you talking to, man?
If I tell you
something's good,
then that's what it is.
내가 하라면 해야지!
Are you going to
take care of this
for me or not?
도와줄 거야
말 거야?
Susan, I swear to God,
it's cool. Trust me.
수잔의 집, 오후 4시 19분
별 거 아니라니까
- 미친 놈!
- 제발 진정 좀 해
Would you fucking calm down?
Hey! Fuck you! Let go of me!
누나는 모른 척 하면 돼
You're not supposed to know
any of this.
딴 데 가서 말하면
난 죽는다고
Jesus, don't say anything,
okay?
You're gonna get me
in a lot of fucking trouble.
갱한테 보복이라도
당한대?
From who, Keith?
From your little fucking
gangster friends from L.A.?
그래...
Yeah! From my...
- 무섭기도 하다
- 진짜야!
Oh, I'm real scared!
Well, you fucking should be.
- 오만가지 주접 다 떨어!
- 왜들 이래?
You're a little
fucking faggot,
you know that?
Whoa, you guys, dude,
what's going on?
- 쟤 납치된 거래
- 아냐!
This kid has been kidnapped!
No, he hasn't!
- 돈이라도 뜯게?
- 직접 물어보든가!
You mean like
"abducted" kidnapped?
Fucking stolen! Ask him.
Yeah.
Yeah, they took me. But
그래, 납치 비슷한데
나는 괜찮아
it's okay.
They took you? Why?
왜 데려왔는데?
Because his scumbag brother
owes Johnny Truelove money.
- 쟤네 형이 돈을 빌렸대
- 닥쳐!
Shut up!
- 이런...
- 멋지다
Whoa!
That's fucking hot.
몸값 같은 거 받으려고?
Dude, so you're like ransom
or something.
그래, 납치된 소년...
Yeah. Stolen boy.
맞아
Yeah.
- 납치된 애 같지 않다
- 그러게
You don't look stolen.
Yeah.
이상한 일이지...
I know. It's weird.
하고 싶은 대로 해
Dude, I want you to know
that you can do anything
you want, okay?
- 그러면 안 돼
- 무슨 상관이야
No, he can't!
I don't play that shit.
전화를 하든가
집에 가든가
You want to fucking leave,
go for it.
You want make a call...
입 좀 닥쳐!
You shut the fuck up,
you fucking bitch!
I'm a fucking bitch?
You're a fucking little bitch!
- 넌 미쳤어
- 가만 안 둔다!
Guys! Whoa! Fuck!
다들 진정해
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Sit down right now,
you fucking bitch!
- 이것 봐
- 가만있어!
I'm gonna knock your ass out.
Keith, fucking chill out!
- 안 그럼 한방 날려 줄 테야!
- 키스, 진정해!
우리 형이 돈 갚을 거야
God, my brother is...
My brother is gonna
pay the money, okay?
봤지?
See?
그때까지 놀까?
So, like, in the meantime,
you're, like, on vacation.
- 그거 좋지
- 정말 멋지다
Yeah. Exactly. Why not?
That's fucking awesome.
- 추억거리가 될 걸
- 멋있어!
It's, like, another story
to tell my grandkids.
Dude, that is so fucking cool.
이 셔츠나 밥 말리 같은
사람이 멋진 거지
Dude, this shirt
is fucking cool.
Bob Marley is cool.
납치가 멋있냐?
You guys think
that kidnapping is cool?
그래, 신나잖아!
Yeah, Susan,
it's fucking exciting!
I think it's romantic,
dude, he's doing this
for his brother.
형을 위해 희생하다니
감동이잖아?
Are you insane?
Susan, chill out.
- 미쳤니?
- 수잔, 진정해
Dude, this is fucking wrong!
이건 미친 짓이야
그렇게 생각 안 해?
Doesn't anybody else think
that this is fucking wrong?
- 아니!
- 수잔, 약이나 먹어!
No!
Susan, take
a fucking Valium! Okay?
- 네가 상관할 바 아니잖아
- 여긴 우리집이라구!
It's not even
any of your business.
No! It is my house!
- 애가 납치됐다고
- 시끄러!
Jesus Christ,
calm the fuck down. All right.
우리 뻑 가는 거나
먹으면서 놀자
I'm going to roll us
the biggest fucking joint
anyone has ever seen.
- 어때?
- 나야 좋지
You down with that, Zack?
Absolutely.
- 이 한심한 멍청이
- 땅꼬마 왔냐?
Hey. What's up,
you blunted faggot?
What's up,
you short bitch?
넌 놀고 있어
난 사업 얘기 좀 하고
Make yourself busy, baby.
We got to talk some business.
- 뭐 좀 마실래?
- 피냐 콜라다
Can I get you guys
a drink?
Pina Colada?
남의 집에 와서
별 걸 다 찾아!
It's not a bar, baby.
There's no
fucking Pina Colada.
Not even a little can?
캔에 든 것도 없어?
No, but I got some wine.
I can make you a spritzer.
와인 있으니까
스프리처 만들어 줄게
Okay.
좋아
앉아
Sit down.
무슨 일이야?
What's the fucking deal?
어떻게 하지?
I don't know what to do.
- 무슨 소리야?
- 그 애 말이야
What do you mean?
About the kid.
잭 때문에 망할 것 같아
We could be
in a lot of trouble.
- 망해?
- 문제가 심각해
Trouble?
Yeah.
Big-ass,
serious-as-shit trouble.
애를 끌고 왔으니
금방 발각될 거고
I mean, you can't
just take a kid
and have no one notice.
내가 말할 땐
똥구멍으로 들었냐!
That's what I told you.
Didn't I say that?
You did, all right?
Fuck!
- 그랬나 봐
- 빌어먹을
But, still,
we are where we are.
Right here, you know?
하여간 해결해야 돼
I mean, it's a big problem
and we got to fix it.
안 들키게 해야 돼
- 어떻게?
- 나도 몰라
So what do we do?
I don't know.
방법이 하나 있는데 차마...
There's an answer here.
There's, like, a solution.
But I'm just...
I'm just not seeing it.
우리 인생 종쳤어
I don't know.
Maybe we're fucked.
종을 쳐?
We're not fucked.
- 그게 무슨 소리야?
- 감방에 처박힐 거라고
What do you mean, fucked?
Jail fucked, motherfucker.
저 자식 집에 가면
나불거릴 텐데
If we let the kid go,
he runs back to Mommy
and Daddy and he rats us out.
Maybe he won't.
Not to mention Tattooey.
- 안 그럴 거야
- 제이크 개자식은!
Who knows what
that crazy motherfucker
is gonna do?
이걸로 평생
날 협박하려 들걸?
We're all gonna be looking
over our fucking shoulders.
I don't think the kid
will spill. I really don't.
- 쟤 아무 말 안할 거야
- 하면 어쩔래?
Yeah, but what if he does?
- 집어치워
- 내 말 알지?
Fuck that shit.
You see what I'm saying?
난 절대 감옥 안 갈 거야
I'm not fucking
going to prison!
Look, I just won't.
- 누군 감옥가고 싶냐?
- 농담 아냐
Yeah. Me neither, bitch.
What the fuck you think
I'm talking about?
I'm not fucking kidding, John.
This is really fucking bad.
제이크부터 끌고와서
해결해야 돼
The best thing we could do
would be to get ahold
of Tattooey,
and to straighten him
and all this shit out
once and for all.
- 제이크 어딨어?
- 낸들 알아?
Well, where is
that motherfucker?
Who the fuck knows, man?
I don't know.
He's probably laying low,
looking to shoot me
in the fucking head.
내 머리통에 총알 박을
궁리나 하고 있겠지
I mean, think about it.
That's what I'd be doing.
내가 생각하는 것처럼
Stop already, all right!
You know how I get
with this anxiety shit.
헛소리 하지 말고
방법을 생각해
(COUGHING)
프랭키?
Frankie?
- 프랭키
- 그래
Frankie?
Yeah.
떨려서 미치겠어
I swear to God, man,
I'm hyperventilating.
I want to ask you something.
궁금한 게 있어
What? Fuck.
뭔데? 젠장
Hypothetically, all right?
혹시나 해서
물어보는 건데
This isn't real, right?
We're just talking here.
상황이 이렇게 됐으니
얘기하는 거야
있잖아...
But...
내가 2,500 달러 주면
애 죽여 줄래?
What would you say if I were
to offer you $2,500
just to kill the kid?
- 죽여?
- 없애는 거지
Kill him?
Yeah, fucking wax him.
완전 미쳤군!
Are you fucking insane?
그런 짓 절대 못해
I'm not going to
fucking kill the kid.
That's a fucking joke, right?
Of course it's
a fucking joke, man!
You're so fucking stupid.
농담 갖고 왜 흥분하니?
You're an asshole, man!
All right, man,
I'm just playing.
- 넌 미쳤어
- 농담이었어
Well, stop fucking around.
그걸 농담이라고 하냐?
그냥...
애를 살살 꼬셔서
Look, man, can't we just
grease the kid?
나중에 말 못하게 하자
You know tell him
he can hang out anytime.
That he's our boy.
내 편으로 만드는 거야!
Throw a fucking arm around him
or something.
- 돈도 몇 푼 주고
- 맞아!
Give him a few bucks?
Right.
여자랑 놀다온 걸로
둘러대라고 시키고
And tell him
when Mommy and Daddy ask,
to say that he ran away
with some girl or something.
그래...
Yeah, maybe, yeah.
I mean, look...
그럴듯한 얘길 만들어서
연습시키는 거야
I mean, we'd have to get
the story straight,
but we can make it work, man.
애만 다독거리면
문제 없을 거야
I know we could.
We just grease the kid.
Yeah.
And then it's taken care of.
Yeah. Yeah.
And that way we're not
running around here like
a bunch of fucking Chinamen.
겁먹고 줄행랑칠
필요 없잖아
Done.
바로 그거야!
난 이래서 네가 좋아
See, that's what I love
about you, man.
나보다 똑똑하거든
You're smarter than me.
(LOUD MUSIC PLAYING)
Fuck!
이런, 어디 봐
Whoa, whoa.
Let me see that.
이리 와
Come here.
- 아프니?
- 아니
Does it hurt?
No.
(CLEARS THROAT)
잭, 얘기 좀 할까?
Could I talk to you alone
for a minute?
무슨 일이야?
What's up?
I just wanted to say
sorry about all this shit.
너한테 몹쓸짓
한 것 같아서
You know, I know that
this is a big pain in the ass.
이런 고생을 시키다니
내가 미쳤지
This whole thing
is really fucking ridiculous.
- 그래
- 힘든 건 없니?
Yeah.
Are you okay?
애들이 잘 대해 줘?
먹는 건 어때?
I mean, is everybody
treating you all right?
I mean, you got enough to eat?
- 좋아
- 그래?
Yeah.
Yeah?
필요한 거 없니?
돈 줄까?
You need anything?
You need some dough?
아니, 괜찮아
No, I'm good.
- 정말?
- 난 잘 지내는 걸
Are you sure? I mean, I...
No, no,
I'm really good. Really.
힘든 거 잘 알아
I mean, I know this is hard,
조금만 참아
곧 해결될 거야
but this is all going to get
squared away soon,
you know, I promise.
All right, cool.
걱정 마
All right.
알았어
나 지금 가야 되는데...
I got to jet, but...
있지, 너 정말
괜찮은 녀석이야
You know something?
You know, you're...
You're a pretty stand-up guy.
- 고마워
- 너희 형이 문제지
Thanks.
I mean, your brother
is a dickhead.
걔는 사랑하는 내 친구지만
I mean, he's my boy
and I love him,
but he's just, you know...
걔는 친구 사이에
바보같이 왜 그러나 몰라
I mean, he's acting
a motherfucking fool
right now, you know.
- 알아
- 그렇지?
Yeah, I know.
Yeah.
Well...
그러니까... 내일쯤이면
Anyways, tomorrow.
This will all be over
by tomorrow.
고생도 끝날 거야
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(PANTING)
엄마
Hi.
밖에서 자고 오랬잖니
Hey, baby. What's up?
I thought you were
spending the night out.
그러려고 했는데...
할 얘기가 있어요
I was. I just...
I really needed to talk.
- 할 얘기?
- 네
Talk?
Yeah.
- 당장?
- 그래요
What, now?
Kind of.
하룻밤!
그것도 일 년에 단 하루
One night. I ask for one night
out of the whole fucking year
아빠랑 단둘이 보내겠다는데
그것도 못 들어주니!
to make love to your father
and you won't even
give that to me?
지금 약에 취해
아무 말도 안 들린다
I'm X-ing right now.
I can't understand
anything you're saying.
I'm sorry, Mom, okay?
Fuck!
- 미안해요, 엄마
- 젠장!
3일 째, 1999년 11월 8일 일요일
오전 11시 26분
He was wearing a brown shirt,
a blue sweatshirt,
brown tennis shoes
갈색 셔츠에 푸른 점퍼
갈색 운동화에...
반지엔 빨간색 알이
박혀있고
and his grandfather's ring.
It has a red stone.
전화 왔어
Baby, you got a phone call.
위에서 받을게
I'll take it upstairs.
알았어
Okay.
실례
Excuse me.
여보세요
Hello. Hello.
Yo. It's me.
The midget.
나야, 땅꼬마
You got some set of balls
calling me here.
전화했으면
말을 해야지?
문자 다 씹을래?
What's the matter?
You don't answer
a motherfucking page?
- 할 얘기 없어
- 그럴 리가
We got nothing to talk about.
Oh, I think we do, don't you?
거래를 마무리하자
Straighten out
all this shit
once and for all?
개소리 집어 치워
네 짓인 거 알아
There's nothing to
straighten out, motherfucker.
I know it was you.
- 무슨 소리야?
- 조니, 다 알아
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Johnny, I know. I know!
넌 죽었어
And you're dead.
- 협박하지 마
- 약속하지
Don't threaten me.
Fuck that! It's a promise.
어디에서 무슨 짓을 하던
쫓아가서 널 잡을 거다
No matter where you go,
no matter what you do,
I'm going to hunt you down.
I'm going to hunt you down,
and then I'm going to
slit your throat
네 목은 내가 따는 거지
and then I'm going
to cut you open
펄떡거리는
네 심장도 먹어주마!
and then I'm gonna eat
your motherfucking heart!
살고 싶음
기도나 하시지
You better pray!
경찰보다 내가 먼저
널 찾아 죽여버릴 거야!
Johnny, you better
fucking pray that the cops
find you before I do!
무릎 꿇고 기도나 해!
Get on your cocksucking knees
and pray!
여보세요!
Hello? Hello?
밥 놀더: 변호사
조니한테 전화요
WOMAN ON INTERCOM:
Mr. Nolder,
Johnny Truelove on two.
Hey, Cock and Balls,
what can I do for you?
- 간 큰 남자, 웬일인가?
- 질문 있어서
Question for you.
누가 돈을 하도
안 갚아서 말이에요
Let's say, someone owes
someone I know money
and won't pay.
돈 꿔간 놈 동생을
납치했다면
So that someone I know
has his boys snatch
the deadbeat's kid brother
till does he does pay.
- 어떤 문제가?
- 큰 문제지
What kind of problems
is he looking at?
Big ones.
몸값을 요구했다면
종신형도 가능하지
If he asks for ransom,
he's looking at life.
듣고 있니?
Hello? You there, Cock?
- 종신형?
- 그래
Life?
Life, yeah.
So what does he do?
I don't know.
- 피할 방법이 없을까요?
- 나도 모르겠네
Probably digs a deep hole.
Why? What's the matter?
Who's in trouble?
어쨌든 큰 사고 친 거야
근데 왜?
쟤는 왜 여기 있는 거야?
SUSAN: What the hell
is he still doing here?
조용하라니까, 수잔
FRANKIE: You got to
chill the fuck out, Susan.
입 잘못 놀려서
이 일 잘못되면
I mean, you keep
running your fucking mouth,
우리도 감옥행이야!
인생 망치는 거라고!
Truelove could go to jail
and we can wind up dead.
그 미친 놈 땜에 말이야
Fuck you, all right.
You don't know.
That motherfucker's crazy.
어제는 2,500 달러 줄테니까
꼬맹이를 죽이래!
Yesterday he offered me
2,500 bucks to kill the kid.
What?
Right. Kill him.
- 뭐?
- 죽이라고!
Oh, Jesus.
이런!
First you give me mouth
and now you give me
fucking tears?
좀 전까지 소리 지르더니
이젠 질질 짜고
너, 가지가지
왕짜증인 거 아니?
Do me a favor, Susan.
Have a period or something.
누가 진짜 죽인대?
조니가 헛소리 한 거야
Of course I'm not going to
do it! I told him. I'm just
saying, that's how spun he is.
다 알아서 할게
I got it under control.
다 알아서 한다고
I got it under control,
all right?
나를 믿는다고 말해 봐
Say it.
Say, "You, Frankie,
have it under control."
말해!
Say it!
- 프랭키, 너를 믿어
- 좋아
You, Frankie,
have it under control.
Right.
Now say "I, Susan,
am a whiny fucking bitch
따라 해, "나 수잔은 질질 짜는
왕짜증 계집애"
"and you, Frankie,
have it under control."
"듬직한 프랭키가
다 알아서 할 거야"
나 수잔은 질질 짜는
왕짜증 계집애
I, Susan, am a
whiny fucking bitch
듬직한 프랭키가
다 알아서 할 거야
and you, Frankie,
have it under control.
좋았어
Right.
일이 꼬여도
나대로 해결 방법이 있지
Worst comes to worst,
I tell everybody
to go fuck themselves
애한테 50달러 줘서
버스 태워 보낼 거야
put 50 bucks
in the kid's pocket,
and stick him on a bus.
- 약속한 거지?
- 그래
You promise?
I swear.
(PHONE RINGING)
이것 봐! 조니야
See, bitch? Johnny. Hey.
Hey, what up?
What's the word?
- 상황 어때?
- 소식은?
We're picking the kid up.
Great! What time?
- 애를 태우러 갈 거야
- 좋아, 몇 시야?
About 8:00, 8:30.
8시나 8시 30분
Listen, man, I'm gonna
have to take him to a hotel
or something, then.
호텔 같은 데로
데려가야겠어
왜 그러는데?
What's going on?
아버지 애인 땜에
도저히 집은 안 돼
My dad's bitch girlfriend
is up my ass
with a fucking broom.
- 도착하면 연락해
- 알았어
Call me when you get there.
All right.
- 됐지?
- 응
Okay?
All right, man.
- 전화 기다린다
- 정리되면 연락 할게
I'm on my cell.
I'll call you
when I get straight.
알았어
All right, later.
애는 집에 간다!
The kid's going home!
지아이모의 집
포모나, 캘리포니아: 오후 9시 6분
What up, buddies?
무슨 일이야?
- 무슨 일이야?
- 이게 누구야!
What up, buddy, buddy?
Buddy, buddy, buddy!
너희 엄마 차 좀 빌려 줘
Hey, we need to borrow
your mom's car.
- 이사 가?
- 그러려고
Moving?
Yeah. Moving.
캘리언트 트로픽스 호텔
팜 데저트, 캘리포니아: 오후 9시 48분
다 왔다, 가자
That one right there.
Yeah, let's go!
어서 내려
Get off me.
You kids have a good time!
딜로어스 스트래튼: 증인 13
재밌게 놀아라
Go!
가자!
(ALL CHEERING)
파티
증인 14-36
돈은 언제 갚을 거야?
MAN: What up?
Well, when am I
gonna fucking get paid?
저쪽으로 가!
Get in there. Get in there.
- 이젠 놀아보자!
- 알았어
You like this shit?
This is dope, right?
Yeah.
모두 나가!
Everybody out.
나가!
화장실인 거 안 보여?
Get the fuck out of here!
Can't you see me
on the toilet?
- 니가 뭐하든 상관없어
- 나가라니까
I don't give a fuck
what you're doing.
I said get the fuck out.
오줌 눌 거야
I'm trying to pee here!
Let go of me!
내 파티란 말이야
저리 가!
This is my party,
and I say
you're getting out.
- 여기서 뭐 하는 거야?
- 이런!
What the fuck
are you doing, crazy-ass?
Hello! Jesus.
저런 꼴을 보다니!
I can't believe
I just saw that.
I don't give a fuck!
잡소리 말고 돈이나 내놔
Listen, to me, Ziggy,
I said, you pay me today.
Oh, you don't have it?
Listen, let me
tell you something.
없어서 못 줘?
한마디만 해주지
If you see me,
you don't want
to fucking see me.
죽고 싶어 환장했구나!
소원대로 해주마, 또라이
Yeah, it's like that,
bitch. Fuck you.
- 전화 끊어
- 끊고 있잖아
Baby, get off the phone.
I'm getting off!
- 누가 속 썩여?
- 왜?
ZACK: Is that guy
giving you a problem?
Yeah, why?
본때를 보여 줘
Let's kick his ass.
갑자기 세졌네?
All of a sudden
you're a tough guy?
나 태권도 검은 띠야
I can fight him.
I'm a fucking black belt
in tae kwon do.
닥쳐
Shut the fuck up.
- 뻥친다
- 진짜야
Your ass.
I am.
나 파트너 잘못 골랐나봐
Looks like I picked
the wrong man.
구라 아냐?
한 번 붙어 봐
No shit. Come here,
you little fucker.
Come on, bitch.
How does that feel?
Think you're bad, huh?
맛이 어떠냐?
죽겠지?
SUSAN: You're going
to break his neck.
그러다 목 부러지겠어
나한테 키스해봐
Give the little fucker
a kiss.
뭐야?
형님 테스트 하냐?
Come on, you're fucking
getting it everywhere!
이젠 어쩔 거야?
What are you gonna
do now, huh?
Who's your fucking daddy, huh?
- 솜씨 한번 보여줘
- 뭐?
Show me
one of your fucking moves.
What?
이 자식 봐라
나랑 한번 해보겠다는 거야?
Well, hell, no, bitch.
Hell fucking no.
You sizing me up?
해보자구?
You sizing me?
That was fucking awesome!
이 꼬마 실력 죽이네!
You're fucking awesome!
Dude.
- 땅콩이 쓸만해
- 형
- 형도 잘하네
- 이 자식 싸움 좀 하는데
That was awesome, dude.
This little bitch can fight!
- 매력 만점이야
- 문 열어!
GIRL: My God,
that was amazing.
KEITH: Open the door!
문 열라고!
Hey, open up, man!
지금 형님들 바쁘다
남자만 붙어
Fuck off! We're fighting.
There's no room for bitches!
가짜 남잔 말고!
Or fucking queers!
- 문 열어!
- 문 열어 줘
Come on,
open the door, assholes!
Okay, open it.
- 살살이 자식
- 입 조심해
FRANKIE:
Let that sack of
monkey shit in here.
Don't call me a sack
of monkey shit.
셔츠는 왜 벗고 난리야?
Jesus, what happened
to your shirt, bitch?
- 몰라, 술 떨어졌어
- 벌써?
I don't know. Dude,
we're out of booze, man.
Already?
Tell your little freeloader
friends to slow
the fuck down, Keith.
개털 자식들
작작 처마시라고 해
I'm not made of money.
나 돈줄 아니거든
I need a cigarette.
All right.
- 담배가 필요해
- 좋아
우린 간다, 알아서들 해
We're leaving.
Keep everything
under control.
안녕
Hey.
- 얘가 걔야?
- 잭, 여기는 알마
Is this him?
Zack, this is Alma.
Watch how fast
I can down this shit.
죽이게 빨리 마시는 거
보여줄까?
별 짓 다하셔!
Holy motherfucking shit.
멋지다
Nice.
한 대 빨고하면
더 빨라
You should have seen me
with the beer bong.
그러지 말고
너희 둘도 해봐
Quit staring at me.
Your turn.
Okay. Ready?
자, 준비
Go.
시작!
- 너 정말 납치당했니?
- 그럴 걸
So you're really stolen?
Yeah. I really am.
귀엽다
He's cute.
You got a girlfriend,
stolen boy?
No.
- 여자 친구 있어?
- 아니
How old are you?
Seventeen.
- 몇 살?
- 17살
17살 웃기시네
15살이면서!
Seventeen?
This motherfucker's
15 years old.
넌 매사에 태클이냐?
Dude,
what's your fucking problem?
미안, 하긴 상관없어
I'm sorry. Jesus.
They don't care anyway, man.
섹스 해 봤어?
Ever been laid, stolen boy?
내 생일이야!
It's my birthday!
Happy birthday, girl.
콘수엘로 멕시코 식당: 클레어몬트, 캘리포니아
오후 10시 17분, 생일 축하해
잠깐 기다려
Can you guys
give us a second?
Why?
I need to talk to you
about something in private.
엘비스한테 할 얘기 있어
Hurry.
서둘러
난 좋아!
GIRL: Love it.
어쩔까?
So?
뭐를?
So what?
어떻게 생각해?
What do you think?
- 어떻게 생각 하냐고?
- 그래
What do I think?
Yeah, what do you think?
뭘 어떻게
생각 하냐는 거야?
What do you mean,
what do I think?
그 자식 말이야
I mean
about this whole thing.
I think no more music videos.
That's what I think.
뮤직 비디오처럼
가짜로 총은 안 쏴!
Right.
좋아
빌어먹을
Fuck it.
필요한 거 있어?
돈 줄까?
You need anything?
Money?
아니
No.
차에 기름은?
You got gas?
만땅이야
I got gas.
그럼 됐네
Okay, then.
Truelove!
조니!
Are you ready to drink
for my birthday?
No, where's he going?
내 생일파티 하는 거지?
엘비스는 어디 가?
I hate it that
you have to work, Schmitty.
일하러 가? 불쌍해라
생일 축하해
케이크 많이 먹어
Happy birthday, Angie.
Eat a piece of cake for me.
Okay.
알았어
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
뭐 해?
멋진 밤을 즐겨야지
What are you doing?
This is your lucky night.
Get in.
나 왔어
Hi.
돌아봐
Turn around.
- 뭐 하려고?
- 그냥 돌아
I don't get it.
Just turn around.
10까지 세기
Start counting.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5...
준비됐지?
One, two, three four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Ready or not, here I come.
- 어딨니?
- 여기
Marco.
Polo!
여기야
- 어디?
- 여기
Marco.
Polo.
여기라니까
(MAN SINGING IN SPANISH)
Do you want to know
what I wished for?
What?
- 무슨 소원 빌었게?
- 뭔데?
I'll tell you.
I want to suck your cock.
Oh, shit.
- 너랑 뜨거운 밤 보내기
- 진짜?
소원성취해라
Wait, the wish is coming true!
It's coming true! Oh, Lordy!
- 내 소원도 들어줄 거지?
- 싫은걸
Wait, my wish is coming true!
My wish is coming true!
Oh, shit!
- 전화좀 하고 올게
- 너무해
Baby, I got to go
make a phone call.
No, you don't.
- 잠깐만 통화하고 올게
- 안 돼, 왜?
I got to make a phone call
for a second.
No. No. Why?
나빴다!
Bad!
- 너무해
- 선물이나 열어봐
He's bad.
Let's open the gifts.
Yes!
맞다!
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
- 여보세요
- 잘하고 있어?
Hello.
What up, jerky?
- 지금 바빠
- 나야
Yeah, I'm kind of busy.
Dude, it's me.
- 조니?
- 그리 가는 길이야
Johnny?
Yeah, I'm on my way.
- 얼마나 걸려?
- 30분, 이따 봐
Oh, great. How long?
Half an hour.
Clear it out, all right?
알았어
Yeah, you got it.
이봐!
잭은 돌려보낼 거야
Hey, hey, hey,
Zack's going home!
파티 끝났어, 해산
Party's over.
All you motherfuckers
got to go.
Bye, Zack. I'm glad
you're going home.
Bye.
- 집에 돌아가서 다행이야
- 안녕
- 고마워
- 오늘밤 잊으면 안 돼!
Thanks.
Now you got
your story to tell.
- 알았어, 안녕
- 또 봐
Yeah, bye.
See you.
- 전화 해
- 그럴게
Call me sometime.
I will.
You better.
꼭 해야 해
안녕
Bye, stud.
그렇게 좋냐?
히죽거리지 좀 마라
And wipe that smile off
your face. You're a dead
fucking giveaway.
알았어
Okay.
세상에
No.
가만있어
Don't fucking move.
What?
왜?
Yo, dude,
just hang out with us.
넌 우리랑 놀다 가
- 이거 타고 집에 갈래
- 한 대 빨고 가
Oh, man, I was going to
catch a ride home.
You love weed.
- 젠장
- 더 놀다 가
Fuck.
You love it.
- 이 몸은 더 놀다갈게!
- 나중에 봐
Fuck you, ladies.
We'll see you guys later,
all right?
운전할 땐 눈 감고!
Drive really fast
with your eyes closed.
너 정말 귀엽다니까
말아놓고 있어
You're an asshole.
Roll up, Stratten.
안녕, 프랭키
Bye, bitches!
We love you, Zack!
네 순결 고마워
ALMA: Thanks for
the virginity, baby!
안젤라의 집: 클레어몬트 북쪽 캘리포니아: 오후 10시 46분
Sonny.
Hey, Elaine, how you doing?
- 소니!
- 잘 지냈어요, 일레인?
Is my boy here?
I'm looking for him.
조니 여기 있소?
지금 찾고 있는데
안젤라 생일 파티 갔는데
No, they went out
for Angela's birthday.
기다려도 될까요?
Something's come up.
You mind if we wait?
- 여기서 뭐 해?
- 잠깐 나와봐
What are you doing here?
Outside.
캘리언트 트로픽스 호텔
팜 데저트, 캘리포니아: 오후 10시 55분
네가 잭을
집에 태워다 줄 거야?
What's the deal, Elvis?
You driving the kid home
or what?
- 무슨 소리야?
- 아냐?
What.
What?
- 맞아
- 도대체 무슨 소리야
That's right.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
What the fuck?
뭐야?
The kid ain't going home.
살려 보내면 안 돼
But I thought
Johnny was going...
Well, you thought wrong.
- 하지만 조니는...
- 작전 바꿨어
Fuck that. Johnny
didn't tell me shit.
The decision's been made.
- 조니는 아무 말 안 했어
- 게임 끝났어
돌았군!
Fuck you.
내가 돌았다고?
너나 그렇지
Fuck me? Fuck you!
조니가 나보고 해결하랬어!
Johnny sent me here
to take care of something
네까짓 게 발악해도
소용없어!
and I'm gonna fucking do it
with you or through you!
이번엔 날 무시 못할 걸!
Who's sucking
whose cock now, huh, Frankie?
- 하려면 너 혼자 해!
- 너도 같이 해야 돼!
Fuck that! I'm out.
Fuck that? You're fucking in.
잔머리 굴리면서
꼬리 빼겠다?
I'm up here to clean up
your mess, and you're gonna
fucking help me,
or the whole world
is gonna come down
on your head.
앞으로 사는 게
고단해질 텐데
All right!
Fucking let go of me!
난 빠질 거야!
나보고 어쩌라고?
What the fuck
do you want me to do?
(DOOR CREAKING OPEN)
테이프 구해와
ELVIS: We need some tape.
Fuck that!
You're gonna dig.
됐어, 니가 해결해
난 절대 못 해
Dig this, bitch!
- 날 도와야 돼
- 난 안 해
You're gonna do it.
You're gonna help me.
Fuck that! No fucking way.
난 더 이상 못 해
네 맘대로 해!
Ain't no fucking way, Elvis.
I'm not digging.
됐어, 여기까지야
Fuck you! I did my shit.
This is the line,
motherfucker!
아무리 막 나간다고
사람까지 죽여?
Everybody's got one
and mine's a fucking grave,
all right?
쏠 테면 쏴
그 총 한 번 맞아보자
You want to shoot me? Shoot me
right fucking here.
I don't give a fuck!
왔어?
Hey, excuse me?
이봐
프랭키는?
나 집에 태워다줘야 돼
Where's Frankie?
I need a ride home.
KEITH: Whoa.
- 무슨 일이야?
- 나 좀 도와줘
What's going on, man?
ELVIS: Come on,
I need your help.
테이프는 뭐 하려고?
What the fuck do you need
duct tape for, dude?
다 어디 갔어?
Where is everybody?
엘비스는
키스 데려다 주러갔어
Keith said he needed
a ride home,
so that guy gave him one.
뭐 보는 거야?
What are you watching?
Austin Powers.
All right.
'오스틴 파워'
재미있다
Shit's so funny.
저러고 2분이나 있네
This shit's been going on for,
like, I don't know,
two minutes.
담배 좀 사올래?
You wanna run
to the store for me?
Get me some cigarettes?
난 어려서 못 살 텐데
Dude, I'm too young
and they won't sell to me.
그럼 드라이브나 갈까?
Let's take a drive,
let's go somewhere.
You want to?
그냥 영화 볼래
No, I'm cool.
I just want to watch a movie.
그래
Okay.
(ANGELA LAUGHING)
안젤라, 어떻게 된 거야?
Angela.
What the fuck is going on?
What did you do?
Nothing.
- 뭐 하다 왔니?
- 별일 없는데
Are you all right?
She's fine.
- 괜찮니?
- 괜찮아요
- 가서 얘기 좀 하자
- 내 생일인데 귀찮게 굴지 마
We're going in the other room,
we need to talk.
Fuck that.
It is my birthday.
No, we're going right now!
Don't you fucking touch me!
- 얘기할 게 있다
- 나 건드리지 마!
- 파티 끝났어
- 젠장!
Hey, the party's over,
wait a second.
Fuck!
엄마한테 말버릇 하곤
You don't talk to your mother
like that.
We're trying to help you!
- 애 어디 있니?
- 누구요?
Where's the kid?
Who?
- 잭 말야!
- 무슨 말씀이세요?
Where's Mazursky?
I don't know
who you're talking...
정말 몰라요
왜 이래요!
Dad, I swear.
Fucking get off me!
정신 나간 놈!
꼴통 자식!
You're fucking stupid!
Stupid, John! Don't you
fucking get it, you moron?
그 애 찾느라고
지금 난리가 났어
There's a Missing Persons
poster on every street corner!
잘못되면 넌 평생
철창신세야
You're in deep shit, Johnny.
The cops pick you up,
you're doing 25 to life.
- 나도 알거든요
- 알면서 왜 이래?
You don't think I know that?
You've fucked
your life up so bad.
The only way you're going
to unfuck it is that
you come clean now, John.
지금도 늦지 않았어
자수해라
You come clean now!
Calm down, calm down.
- 자수하라고!
- 진정하세요
내가 말해 볼게요
Let me talk to him, all right?
Come on, let me talk to him.
이 상황에선 누구도
흥분하기 마련이야
Look, everybody's
getting excited here.
아버지도 생각한 게
있어서 그러는 거야
What your father's
trying to say is
we have a plan.
일단 꼬마를 데려오고
여기 앉아서
You bring the kid home,
we have a sit-down.
나, 너, 부모님
모두 의논하자
Me, you, the mother,
the father, everybody.
돈 문제는 아빠가
해결할 거야
Sonny brings his checkbook,
and we settle it right there.
- 안 돼요
- 확신은 못하겠다만
That will never work.
I'm not saying it will.
어차피 감옥은
피할 수 없을 거다
You're probably looking
at some jail time.
그래도 우리가 제안하는 건
But if that's
our only option,
변호사인 나와 같이
경찰에 가는 거야
I'll walk you
right through custody,
we'll do it the right way.
I guarantee you do
minimum sentence.
그럼 형량을
줄이는 건 가능해
Be smart, kid.
Let the spooks
do the hard time.
미련한 짓 말고
맘 돌려라
Fuck that. No jail.
감옥엔 절대 못 가
2년? 껌값이야
겨울, 여름, 겨울, 여름, 끝!
Two years? A piece of cake.
Winter, summer,
winter, summer, done.
- 싫어요
- 그럼 어쩌려고?
No.
Then you tell us
your plan, Einstein.
어떻게 할 건지 말해봐
You tell us
how this all turns out.
- 키스, 무슨 일이야?
- 넘어졌어
Hey, Keith, what's up?
I fell.
그래?
You fell?
손대지 마
Hey.
Don't fucking touch me.
- 무슨 일인데?
- 반갑다
What's up?
What's up, buddy?
You're Zack, right?
Yeah.
- 네가 잭이지?
- 그래
난 엘비스야
곧 집에 데려다줄게
Well, I'm Elvis
and I'm going to
take you home, man.
같이 할 거지?
You coming?
너도 해야 돼
You got to do this, man.
이젠 되돌릴 수 없어
It's got to be unanimous.
저 자식 살려두면
우린 평생 끝장이야
If the kid goes home,
everybody's looking at life.
Life?
Life.
- 평생?
- 그래
변호사가 종신형 이랬대
We talked to a lawyer, man,
and there's no way around it.
웬 종신형?
애 돌봐준 것 뿐인데
Life for what?
For taking care of the kid?
재워주고 먹여줬다고
감옥 가냐!
For letting him sleep
at my fucking house?
처음부터 같이 있어놓고
You were there
from square one.
이제 빠질 수
있을 것 같냐?
You sat on him the whole
fucking time. You think
you're going to walk?
- 평생?
- 그렇다니까
Goddamn. Life?
There it is.
I mean, I like the kid.
저 자식 정들었는데
어린놈이니 그렇지
What's not to like?
15살이잖아
He's 15.
살려둔다고 될 거 같아?
He's just too much
of a liability.
애를 보내주면
제이크가 가만 둘 거 같아?
Think about it.
We send the kid home,
you got Jake looking for you.
그런 건 원하지 않지?
You don't want that.
지금 내빼면
조니가 널 죽일 걸
You don't go along,
then Johnny don't trust you
and he's coming after you
소니 아저씨는 어떻고?
and you sure as shit
don't want Sonny Truelove
knocking at your door.
We don't have a choice, man.
이 방법뿐이야
집에 가면
엄마 아빠한테 죽었다
God, my parents
are going to fucking kill me.
엄마를 만나면 그냥...
I can just see my mom.
She's fucking...
그러니까...
젠장
Oh, God. Oh, God.
근데 절대 걱정 마
But, hey, guys, listen,
I would never
rat you guys out.
절대 형들 얘기 안 할게
You guys and me are like...
We're like this.
You know that, right?
나한테 무지 잘해줬잖아
프랭키 형, 알잖아?
Frankie, you know that,
right?
물론 알지
Yeah, we know that, man.
그렇지?
Right. Cool.
도망 나왔다고 둘러댈게
I'm probably
just going to say that I...
그냥 여기 저기
놀며 떠돌아다녔다고
I don't know,
that I ran away
or something to, like,
애들이 좋아하는
베이커스 필드 같은 데 말이야
Bakersfield or Fresno
or something.
알지?
Fuck it, you know?
베이커스 필드
아는 사람 없어?
Hey, does anybody know
where Bakersfield is?
Say you were with a girl.
They'll believe that.
여자랑 같이 있었다고 해
그럼 믿을 거야
맞아, 줄리 같은 애랑
Yeah, like Julie.
집에 가면
새롭게 시작할 거야
You know, when I get back,
I'm going to start fresh.
You know that?
처음부터 다시 시작하는 느낌
프랭크 형도 알아?
Like, I just want to start
completely fresh. You ever
feel like that, Frankie?
What's up?
Like...
- 뭐라고?
- 있잖아...
Like, I don't know. Like you
want to, I don't know,
go to Europe or something.
유럽 여행 계획도 짜고
Or take a class, or something
like that. Or learn to play
an instrument. Like guitar.
다른걸 배우거나...
기타 같은 악기는 어떨까?
난 악기 다루는
재주가 꽝인데...
It sounds really fucking hard.
I mean, it's guitar.
뭐 하나 잘하는 게
없거든
But it bugs me
that I don't know
how to do anything, you know.
그래도 한 가지 정도는...
I'm pretty sure I could.
Yeah.
- 애한테 손대지 못하게 해!
- 아무 일 없을 거예요
Johnny, call it off.
Nothing's gonna happen.
These guys are such fuck-ups,
the kid's probably loose
right now.
그 멍청이들이
무슨 짓을 하겠어요!
Make the fucking call!
당장 전화해!
여기는 왜?
ZACK: What are we doing?
- 너 데려다 줄 사람 만나러
- 좋아
ELVIS: We're meeting somebody
who's gonna take you home.
Oh, cool.
You know, I think I'm going to
start being nicer to my mom.
이젠 엄마 말도 잘 들을래
계집애 같은 말이지만
엄마는 말야...
It's kind of gay,
but if you think about it,
she's the shit.
엄마는 세상에서
가장 좋은 친구거든
She's, like, my best friend
in the whole world, you know?
- 안녕
- 안녕하세요
Hi.
스콧과 데비 서블렛
증인 37, 38
도저히 못 하겠어
난 갈래
I can't do this.
I can't do this, man.
I got to fucking go home.
이봐, 키스?
Come on, Keith.
키스?
Keith?
근데 왜 울어?
Dude, what's going on?
You're crying.
(SOBBING)
Get away from me!
Hey!
- 비켜!
- 야!
키스!
ZACK: Keith?
대체 왜 저래?
What's the matter
with him?
키스?
Him?
프랭키, 무슨 일이야?
Frankie, what's going on?
Frank?
프랭키
프랭키!
Frankie?
왜 이래?
Dude.
- 이봐
- 준비됐지? 해치우자
Oh, man!
All right, you ready?
Let's do this.
- 내가 뭘 잘못했어?
- 입 닥쳐!
Oh, man, please,
I didn't do anything.
Move it. Shut the fuck up.
- 제발 부탁이야
- 진정하고 저리 가
I swear to God, please.
Relax! Move, move, move.
- 프랭키 제발
- 진정해, 아무것도 아냐
Frankie, please.
Relax, buddy, relax, okay?
- 네가 생각하는 거 아냐
- 그런 거 같은데!
It's not what you think, okay?
Yeah, it is, Frankie!
- 우리 친구 아냐?
- 친구 맞아
Please,
I thought we were boys.
We are boys.
Frankie, there's nobody
up there!
Nobody is picking me up!
저긴 아무도 없어
나 데리러 온 사람 없다구!
- 아냐, 일단 조용히 해
- 약속하는 거지?
Yes, there is, okay.
Just stop freaking out.
Frankie, you promise?
- 약속할게
- 맹세할 수 있어?
I promise, all right?
Do you swear?
목숨 걸고 맹세할게
별 일 없어
Zack, everything's cool,
on my life, okay,
I swear to God.
- 자
- 좋아
Come on.
Okay.
- 제발 진정해
- 알았어
All right, I swear to God.
All right.
Come on, man.
All right, man.
- 그냥 걷기만 해
- 알았어
Let's just walk.
All right.
그냥 걷기만 하면 돼
We're just going
to take a walk.
Come on, man.
아무한테도 말 안할게
제발 죽이지 마
Frankie? Oh, please!
I won't tell anybody,
I swear to God, Frankie!
도저히 못 하겠다
Hey, we're not gonna
do this, right? We're not
really gonna do this.
Shut your fucking mouth!
We're not gonna do this?
- 입 닥쳐!
- 꼭 이렇게 해야 해?
If you want to live,
shut your mouth.
Please, mister! Please!
- 살고 싶으면 입 다물어
- 제발 살려줘!
FRANKIE: Are you crazy?
This is fucking stupid, man.
바보 같은 짓 하지마
Goddamn it, Frankie,
I can't fucking concentrate!
네가 떠들어대니까
정신만 헷갈리잖아!
엄마한테도 말 안 할게
I swear I won't tell
my mom or anything!
시끄럽게 굴면 쏜다!
Shut his fucking mouth
or I'll fucking shoot him!
- 진짜야, 쏴버린다!
- 알았어, 알았다구
I mean it!
I'll fucking shoot him!
All right! All right!
형들 힘들게 절대 안 할게
맹세해!
You'll never see me again!
I swear!
- 제발 조용히 해
- 알았어
Look, little man,
you got to calm down,
all right?
Okay?
Okay.
- 다 긴장해서 그래
- 죽고 싶지 않아
Everybody's nervous,
all right?
I don't want to die, Frankie.
- 진정해
- 알았어
Okay?
Okay.
- 좋아
- 그래
Okay?
All right.
별 일 없을 거야
Everything's okay.
Okay.
- 알았지?
- 프랭키
All right?
Frankie.
What's the tape for,
Frankie?
근데 테이프는 뭐야?
- 해치지 않을 테니 걱정 마
- 알았어
I would never hurt you,
Zacky, all right?
Okay.
테이프로 살짝 손을
감는 거 뿐이야
But I'm going to have to
tape you up.
So give me your hands.
- 알았어
- 아무 일 없을 거야
Okay.
Everything's going
to be all right.
- 나만 믿어, 친구잖아
- 알아
Hey. Hey, I'm your boy.
I know.
- 알았어
- 괜찮지?
Okay.
All right?
별 일 아니라니까
See? Everything's okay.
Everything's okay.
I don't want to die, Frankie.
I don't want to die.
난 죽기 싫단 말야!
입에 테이프 붙일게
Now I'm gonna
have to tape
your mouth up, okay?
그래
All right.
알았어
Okay.
누가 친구한테
나쁜 짓을 하겠니?
You're my boy.
I wouldn't hurt you.
괜찮지?
Okay?
- 걱정 마
- 알았어
Hey, everything's okay.
All right. I know.
- 준비됐지?
- 응
You ready?
Yeah.
뭐 하는 거야?
What the fuck are you doing?
(ZACK SOBBING)
(ZACK GRUNTING)
FRANKIE: Oh, fuck.
넌 미쳤어
Oh, Jesus fucking Christ.
완전히 돌았어
아침 6시였는데
It was 6:00 in the morning
검정색 차 몇 대가 오더니
and several black cars
pulled up.
양복 입은 남자들이
현관 벨을 막 눌렀어요
There were men in suits
and the doorbell
was just ringing.
올리비아 마주르스키 - 카마릴로 주립병원
드디어 잭을 찾았다고는 했는데...
"We found your son,"
they said.
우리 아들을 찾긴 했는데...
"We found your son and it's
나쁜 소식이라고
그들이 말했어요
"bad news," they said.
장례식은요?
INTERVIEWER:
About the funeral?
- 제이크는 왔나요?
- 안 왔죠
Jake didn't show?
No.
Oh, he said it was
out of respect for me.
That's a crock.
나를 위해 안 온다나?
솔직히 죽을까봐
겁난 거지
He just didn't
want to get hit.
- 이해가 좀 안 되네요
- 총 맞을까봐...
I'm sorry,
I don't understand.
Shot. Killed. Murdered.
마약 딜러한테
5만 달러를 못 갚았대요
I happen to know
he owes $50,000
to one drug dealer.
마약 세계란 게 그런 건지
They have their own rules
in the drug world.
그깟 돈 1,200 달러 때문에
애를 죽이다니!
They killed my son
for $1,200.
뭐라 위로의 말씀을
드려야 할지
I'm just so sorry
for your loss. I mean,
I can't even imagine.
When my son died, I died.
잭이 죽은 순간
나도 죽은 거예요
평생 그 애만을
사랑했는데
I loved him
every single day of my life
그 애만을 위해 산 건데
and I wasn't afraid
to show him.
무엇이 자살 기도를
하게 만들었나요?
What made you try
and kill yourself?
나도 몰라요
I don't know.
내가 죽을 때 까지는
많은 시간이 남았겠죠
You know,
it seemed like a long time
to my natural death.
I don't know.
모르겠어요
세 번의 자살 기도에는
술의 영향이 있었어요
You know, all three times
I tried to commit suicide,
there was alcohol involved.
병원에서 자살하려고 했을 때
잘 안됐어요
When I tried to kill myself
in the hospital,
I did it wrong.
이렇게 했을 거라고
생각하겠죠?
You know,
you're supposed to
do it like this.
약물 때문인지도 모르죠
Maybe it was the pills.
It's all bullshit, anyway.
어쨌든 다 헛수고였어요
이렇게 떠들더군요
They say
모든 고통에는
의미가 있다고...
there's a reason
for everything.
Well,
자식이 죽었는데
그따위 소리가 나와?
if that God's
got a purpose for me,
이 고통의 의미가 뭔지
말이나 해 봐!
he better get
the fuck down here
and tell me what it is!
난 모르겠단 말야!
Because I don't see it.
오늘은 여기까지 밖에
못 하겠어요
I think that might be enough
for today. Okay?
- 시간 내주셔서 감사합니다
- 네
Thank you for your time.
Okay.
- 괜찮겠어요?
- 네
Was that okay?
Yeah.
미안해요
Okay. I'm sorry.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Yo, what's up?
무슨 일이야?
잭이 죽었어
Zack's dead.
어떻게 알아?
How do you know that?
난 모르는 일이야
I had nothing
to do with this.
아무 짓도 안 했다고
I never laid
a finger on him.
이 자식 죽은지도 몰랐어!
I didn't know
this happened, Susan!
나도 못 믿겠어
I can't believe it happened.
- 어떻게 된 거야?
- 나도 몰라
Fucking what is going on,
Frankie?
I don't know.
Tell me the truth!
I don't know, okay!
- 바른대로 말해!
- 몰라
누가 날 모함하나보지!
I think I'm getting set up!
잭을 데려다 줬어?
Did you
fucking take him home?
당연하지
Yes! I dropped him off
in Pomona.
어디로 갔는데?
집 앞에 내려준 거야?
Where? What street?
You dropped him off
at his fucking house?
걔가 말하는 곳에
내려줬다고!
I don't fucking know, okay?
I dropped him off in Pomona!
당장 변호사나 찾아 봐
You better get yourself
a good lawyer.
빌어먹을
Fuck you!
여기 오면 어떡해?
나까지 물 먹일래?
You can't come in here, man.
I'm serious, man.
Get the fuck out of here.
- 나 큰일 났어
- 엄마 차로 그 짓을 한 거야?
I'm in trouble, Pick.
Yeah, no shit.
And with my mom's car, man!
- 왜 그런 짓을 했어!
- 미안해
Why'd you do it, huh?
I'm sorry.
너 땜에 내가 얼마나
개고생 했는지 알아?
Motherfuckers.
Do you have any idea
how much fucking shit
I've been through
for this?
I'm fucked, Pick.
You gotta help me, man.
Can you just give me your car?
나 감방가게 생겼어
차 좀 빌려줘
당장 꺼져
No, man. Fuck that!
- 차 좀 태워줘
- 당장 꺼지랬다
Can you give me
a ride out of town?
No. Get the fuck
out of here, man!
- 어디로 가란 거야?
- 꼴리는 대로, 꺼져
Where the fuck
do you want me to go?
That's your fucking problem.
그럼 전화 좀
조니한테 연락해야 돼!
Man, you got to let me use
your phone. I gotta call
Johnny. Please. Please.
절대 못 도와줘, 제발 가
Look, man, I love you,
but you're on your own.
(SIRENS WAILING)
Put your hands behind
your head, or I'll blow your
fucking head off! Get down!
손 머리 뒤로
움직이면 발포한다
- 난 너랑 같이 있지도 않았어
- 어서 엎드려
I'm not fucking with you,
asshole! Get down
on the ground, now!
당장 꿇어!
Get on your knees,
asshole.
경찰이 티코도 잡아간 거야?
I can't believe it.
They got Tiko, too?
티코, 엘비스, 911
다 끌어갔다고
Yeah. Tiko, Elvis,
Nuts, 911.
They got everybody.
왜?
Well, for what?
몰라 물어?
꼬맹이가 죽었잖아
What the fuck
do you think, baby?
That kid turned up dead.
복장 멋지네요
Hey, the Captain
and Tennille.
- 어떻게 오셨나요?
- 저 차랑 이거랑 교환합시다
What can I do for you guys?
Hey, I'd like to
trade that for that.
- 이 차를 저거랑?
- 네
You want to trade
this car for that car?
Yeah.
- 그럼, 결제는?
- 현금 박치기로
All right.
Let's go get you a loan app.
We don't need to do that.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
글렌 카프리 모텔
앨버커키, 뉴멕시코: 11월 30일
You want to fuck?
섹스 할까?
그러든가
All right.
(MOANING)
- 문제 있어?
- 아니
Something wrong?
No.
물컹거리는데 어떻게 해?
No? Your dick's
not even hard.
- 기다려 봐
- 기다리라고?
It's getting there.
Getting there?
- 그래
- 풍선껌 같잖아
Yeah, it's getting there.
It's like a piece
of bubble gum.
그럼 네가 주물럭하든가
Then do something
about it, bitch.
(SIGHING)
미안
Sorry.
미안?
이젠 사내구실도 못 하니?
Sorry? Yeah, you're
a sorry little bitch
who can't even fuck!
머리가 너무 복잡해서
그렇단 말이야
Excuse me for being
a little distracted,
all right!
숨 돌릴 시간 좀 줘
Give me a break.
I've got a lot
on my mind right now.
그럼 뭐 할래?
카드놀이?
Well, what do you want
to fucking do?
You want to play cards?
그냥 껴안고 있을까?
You want to cuddle?
- 그럼 그거 말고...
- 난 섹스하고 싶다고
Can't we just...
No, fuck that shit!
I want to fuck!
- 네가 잘하면...
- 해봤자 안 되잖아
Hey, suck my dick, all right?
I tried that.
It didn't work, did it?
- 망할 년
- 입 좀 닥치지
You're a fucking bitch.
Shut the fuck up.
밝히긴 더럽게 밝혀!
You know that?
You're a fucking cunt.
- 내 신발 어딨어?
- 몰라
Where's my fucking shoe?
I don't know.
알았어, 내 담배 줄까?
Okay, all right, all right.
Fucking truce.
Do you want one of mine?
됐어
바람 쐬고 올게
Fuck you. I'm taking a walk.
뉴 마켓 할인매장
앨버커키, 뉴멕시코
(SIRENS WAILING)
버즈의 집: 에스파놀라, 뉴멕시코
버즈, 조니가 왔어
Buzz! Johnny's here.
Johnny who?
조니 누구?
BUZZ: Yeah,
it was unbelievable.
저도 믿을 수 없었어요
고등학교 졸업 후
처음 봤으니
I hadn't seen Johnny
since junior high.
아닌 밤중에
홍두깨인가 싶었죠
I mean, what a coincidence,
right? I look up
and he's right there.
왜 왔는지 말하던가요?
Did he tell you
what happened?
버즈 펙스키: 로스앤젤레스, 캘리포니아
2003년 3월 27일: 네, 대충 말해줬어요
Yeah. He told me
that some friends of his
나쁜 짓 하다 걸려서
도망간다고요
had done some bad shit
and that he was
going down for it.
외국으로 튀어야 한다나?
He said that he was
in big trouble. He needed help
to get out of the country.
- 그 얘기만 믿고 도와줬나요?
- 그럼요
And you agreed to drive him,
just like that?
Yeah.
친한 친구였으니까요
He's my boy. He was stuck.
All right. Go on.
계속 해봐요
좋아요
All right.
이쪽으로 가고 있는데
이 친구가 이상한 거예요
So we go up by l-25, right?
And this guy is acting
fucking weird, dude.
제발 용서해 달라면서
미친 소리나 해대고
Talking about God
and forgiveness,
all kinds of crazy shit.
국경 가까이 오니
완전 미치더군요
So we get to the border
crossing and he starts
flipping out, going crazy.
진정하고 말하고
I'm like, "Dude,
fucking calm down, bro.
차가 멈출 테니 트렁크에
들어가라고 했더니
"We'll stop, we'll pull over,
you'll get in the trunk.
It's all good."
놈들이 잡으러 온다면서
광분하더군요!
He's like, "No, no, no!
They know! They know!
I'm serious! I'm fucked."
정신병자 뺨치는
수준이었는데
I'm, like... You should have
seen it. He was
going out of his mind.
그래서 차를 돌렸더니
멕시코로 가자고 하더군요
So we turn around,
we turn around again.
Now he wants to go to Mexico.
부랴부랴 거꾸로 갔는데
So we go
all the way back down,
we're driving back down.
또 마음을 바꿔 싫다더군요
We get to Cheyenne.
He changes his mind again.
난 도저히 더는 못한다고
I'm like,
"All right, dude, that's it.
I can't do this forever.
한 군데만 말하라고 했죠
"Where the fuck
do you want to go?"
(POLICE RADIO CHATTERING)
- 곧 나올게
- 알았어
Be right back.
Okay.
딱 5분이면 돼
Hey, I mean it,
all right. Five minutes.
기다릴게
All right.
I'll wait for you.
납치에 가담한 티코는
공범죄로 9년 형을 선고 받았다
키스는 2급 살인죄를 적용
25세까지 청소년 보호소에 수감됐다
프랭키에게도 살인 공범죄가 적용
종신형을 선고받았다
엘비스는 납치 및 1급 살인죄를 적용
사형선고를 받고 집행 대기 중이다
지난 4년간 아드님
도주를 도왔을 테니463>
INTERVIEWER:
It's been four years
since your son's escape,
and you know what?
어디 있는지
확실히 아시겠군요
I think you helped him.
I think you know
exactly where he is.
드디어 올 것이 왔군
There it is.
Million dollar question,
right?
What you, the cops, the D.A.,
the Feds, what everybody
wants to know, right?
경찰, 검찰, FBI
다 그렇게 생각하죠
누가 탈출을 도왔고
Somebody had to help him
get out of the country.
돈도 보낼 겁니다
Somebody has to be
sending him money.
I do not know
where my son is.
걔가 어디 있는지
전혀 몰라요
안다고 해도
지금 털어 놓겠소?
And if I knew, you think
I'd tell you
and this fucking camera?
- 사라진 거요
- 뭐요?
I think he's lost.
What?
그날 먹을 걸 주려고
냉장고를 열었는데
The day they dropped him off
at my house, I reached into
the fridge to get a sandwich,
돌아보니 애가 없더군요
I turned around,
he was gone.
- 말도 안 돼요
- 정말이오
Come on.
I'm telling you, he's lost.
그게 마지막이었던 셈이지
I think he's right.
I mean, I ain't seen him.
He ain't here.
여기에도 없으니
사라진 거죠
He must be lost.
Now get the fuck
out of my house.
이제 꺼져 주시지
조니는 5년간
FBI의 추적을 받았고
인터폴에 의해 2005년 8월 10일
파라과이에서 체포됐다
현재 재판 대기 중이며
유죄가 확정되면
사형을 피할 수 없을 것이다